<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Zara RW Storm</title>
    <link href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm" />
    <updated>1969-12-31T17:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Zara RW Storm</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Unforgiven (Ghost Crimes #4)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Zara RW Storm</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/unforgiven/"/>
        <id>https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/unforgiven/</id>
            <category term="Ghost Crimes"/>

        <updated>2021-09-06T21:22:17-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Content Warning: Stalking, Police, Lesbophobia, Creepy Comments From A Man About a Lesbian, Magical Ritual, Mental Contact, Psychedelia, Spirit Possession Star tried to hold their breath as they entered the peach perfume dominated back of Raised Spirits, but the best they could do was hold&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p class="align-center">Content Warning: Stalking, Police, Lesbophobia, Creepy Comments From A Man About a Lesbian, Magical Ritual, Mental Contact, Psychedelia, Spirit Possession</p>
<hr>
<p>Star tried to hold their breath as they entered the peach perfume dominated back of Raised Spirits, but the best they could do was hold back their reaction. The creaking of the ceiling fan was threatening to break their attention and release a reaction to the scent.</p>
<p>They had only been here once before. The owner, Zlata, had introduced them to their first client here months ago, it looked no different, not even the papers and crystals strewn about the desk, a big wooden slab.</p>
<p>The space around the was meticulous and clean, bare of even dust. A tall lamp beside the desk illuminated the space with just too bright light. Her hair was short and black, framing her wrinkled face reading the papers on her desk.</p>
<p>“You helped Lyuba,” Zlata said, a thick russian accent to her voice. “She told me that you gave her a sense of closure.”</p>
<p>She turned her attention to Star, staring up with dark eyes, her face unmarked by makeup. She wore several beaded bracelets and necklaces over her plain white shirt hanging loosely on her body.</p>
<p>Beside her desk, stood their friend, Silvia. Her dark brown hair was long on her left side, hanging down to just below her chin and cut short on the other side. She had crossed her well muscled arms and stared at her feet.</p>
<p>Their eyes lingered the low cut of her black shirt with the Raised Spirits logo emblazoned on it and to the skin between her thigh high boots and her modest black skirt hanging down just below her knees. They did their best to look away.</p>
<p>“Yes, ma’am. I did my best,” Star said. “But that was months ago. Why talk about this, now?”</p>
<p>“Silvia here,” Zlata motioned to Silvia who was fidgeting beside the desk, “tells me that you don’t just help the living, but also the dead.”</p>
<p>“That’s true,” Star chewed on their lower lip. “Do you have someone who needs help?”</p>
<p>“I will pay double your standard rate because Silvia likes you.”</p>
<p>Star looked aside slightly. They wished they had something to cover their blush. They looked back and Silvia’s cheeks were flushed red.</p>
<p>Zlata continued, “For several years, a local musician called River performed here regularly when we have live music. Last year, xe unfortunately died in a car crash. It was an accident and it was all very sad. I was at xer funeral.”</p>
<p>“And what help would River need of me?”</p>
<p>“I only know the broad strokes, you’d have to ask xer for detail,” Zlata said. “But my understanding is that xe has had a... stalker. Over the past few months, someone has kept going to psychics asking to see xer and, eventually, xer stalker started doing the seances himself. Xe finds it all very unwelcome.”</p>
<p>Star frowned. “And how did you come to know about this?”</p>
<p>Zlata smiled. “Ah, River knew my propensity to spirituality. Xe visited me in a dream and I asked Silvia if she knew how I could help, so she recommended you.”</p>
<p>“I believe I can help with this,” Star said. “And you’re right. I will need to speak with xer. Not just to get more information, but also to build out a safehouse.”</p>
<p>“I have given Silvia a few days of paid leave,” Zlata said, “including making up for lost tips. I can afford it and I would rather you have all the help that you need.”</p>
<p>Silvia’s face was affixed with a strained smile.</p>
<p>Star gave a slight bow. “Thank you for bringing this to my attention and giving me what I need to solve this problem. I’d be happy to help out.”</p>
<p>Zlata waved her arm across her desk and Star fled the backroom. They got halfway out from behind the bar when they felt a warmth on their shoulder.</p>
<p>“Star...” Silvia trailed off.</p>
<p>They held their breath for a few moments. “Yes?”</p>
<p>Several more moments passed before Silvia said, “My motorcycle is out back. I’ll show you to the back exit.”</p>
<p>They left together while Star texted Ezra. Silvia stopped at her motorcycle.</p>
<p>“Thanks.” Silvia smiled to Star. “For helping with this, I mean. I knew River, too. We used to chat after xer shows.”</p>
<p>“I’m happy that it’d be for you, too,” Star said. “But I’m doing this for xer, not for you and certainly not for Zlata.”</p>
<p>“I appreciate that.”</p>
<p>She mounted her motorcycle and Star got on behind. They set off for their apartment together.</p>
<hr>
<p>Star’s apartment was barely larger than Zlata’s office, but it was free of scents and sounds, with only a small ceiling light, off to allow sunlight to dominate the space.</p>
<p>There was a kitchinette in one corner and a mattress on the floor to the side. The floor was bare and dusty, long neglected by Star’s tight budget. Despite this, their kitchenette had been well stocked for weeks and a small chair had been added to the corner, comfortable, but not big enough to share with guests.</p>
<p>They had set out their meditation mat, with sigils on it forming a circle, and Silvia had set out candles around them. By now, this had become a routine for the two of them.</p>
<p>Star closed their eyes and they heard a lighter in front of them.</p>
<p>They chanted, “River! River! River!”</p>
<p>The lighter clicked and the light that fell on their closed eyes went dark.</p>
<p>“River! River! River!”</p>
<p>The lighter clicked and the room cooled.</p>
<p>“River! River! Ri-”</p>
<p>They were River.</p>
<p>“No, no, no, no, not ag-” Their eyes flew open and there was Silvia crouched in front of them holding a lighter.</p>
<p>“Oh,” they said. “Silvia.”</p>
<p>They rose and threw their arms around their friend who returned the gesture.</p>
<p>“I guess Zlata got the message.”</p>
<p>“Yeah. She asked me who I knew who could help and I told her about my friend, Star, here.”</p>
<p>They broke the hug. “Oh, is that the friend you told me ab-”</p>
<p>“Yes,” Silvia cut in. “And they can hear everything you say.”</p>
<p>Star came back to the front. “And you don’t need to stay in my body. I’ll have some questions for you in a bit, but, for now, I’m going to get this place warded, once a friend of mine gets here, so that you’ll be safe.”</p>
<p>They were only Star.</p>
<p>“How long will Ezra take?”</p>
<p>Star shrugged. “Let me check my phone.”</p>
<p>They checked their phone and they had no messages after Ezra said it was on its way. They shook their head.</p>
<p>“Damn. It’d be nice to have it here.”</p>
<p>“Well,” Star said, “I’m sure it’ll be here soon. Until then, what is it that you told River about that you had to cut xer off?”</p>
<p>“Oh.” Silvia cleared her throat. “Well, I told her about the, ah, amazing things you’re able to do. That’s all. And that wasn’t me cutting xer off. Just letting xer know the situation.”</p>
<p>“I’m not sure I’m convinced that was all,” Star said, ”but I won’t press you.”</p>
<p>“Thanks.” Silvia did her best to smile. “I...”</p>
<p>She trailed off. They were saved from an awkward silence by a knock at the door.</p>
<p>Silvia rose. “I’ll get that.”</p>
<p>She walked past Star. They turned and the door was open. In stepped a tall, lanky person with spiked hair, now dyed deep purple, wearing black fishnet stockings on its arms under a simple black t-shirt and simple black slacks.</p>
<p>“Oh, hey, Ezra,” they said. “I was just waiting for you to get here so that we can get to work on warding this apartment.”</p>
<p>They explained to Ezra what the latest case was and the three of them got to work.</p>
<p>They worked on drawing out sigils of Ezra’s design, a circle broken at the top and bottom with a square inscribed within it and a spiral from one of the corners of the square down to the middle. The sigils were designed to both keep energy and spirits within the apartment in the apartment as well as to break external rituals. They served to draw unconscious connection between what was being attempted and the location they were to be placed.</p>
<p>Star and Silvia went around the apartment using tacks to pin the sigils to the walls of the apartment at regular locations while Ezra worked on a larger replica of the sigil.</p>
<p>They returned to the center of the apartment where Ezra was laying out the larger sigil.</p>
<p>“So,” Star said, “what do we do at this point?”</p>
<p>“Now the two of us,” Ezra said, “meditate on either side of the sigil holding hands. We’ll be intermingling our energy by doing that and begin to infuse it into the central sigil. Then, I’ll begin to form a servitor, a magical construct, in order to maintain the spell’s structure without either of us needing to keep our mind on its maintenance.”</p>
<p>It pulled a knife out from its bag.</p>
<p>“Finally, I’ll use this to form a shallow cut on my hand along with an incantation and use the energy from my blood to give life to this servitor,” it said, “This is necessary because I want to give it a lot of power, and this is what I tend to use for that. Other things can be used to add extra power, such as fire, and still other things can be used to aid in the concentration, like incense. If we were making this to last, I’d recommend using multiple methods of increasing power and aiding in concentration. This is only designed to last for about a week.”</p>
<p>They sat with the sigil between them and took each others hands. They breathed in and out in tandem with Ezra. It’s hand was cold, like a hard metal, its fingers sharp needle heads. The cold went up the whole of its arm, twisted like mess of cables. They traveled along each cable and they all terminated at a central core in the middle of its chest where they twisted into a tight knot.</p>
<p>Cold went up their arm, a metal cable sliding up it and into them, then it continued out of them, out-flowing from their mouth like water from a fountain dropping straight down to the ground. From the knot they found, they grew out of it, bursting out like a sapling coming out of the ground in spring. They hung down to touch the sigil.</p>
<p>The out-flowing cables wove around the sapling they had formed and then broke off from the cables pouring out and the wood still growing. The cables molded the composite of metal and wood, giving it two legs, a head, and one arm with a shield the size of the body and the shape of a kite.</p>
<p>The cold metal touching their hands moved away, but they continued to flow in. There was pressure on the middle of the metal palm and then pain. Black oil drained from the metal and fell upon the creature between them. It shook and then stirred.</p>
<p>“Loyal homunculus,” they spoke, both mouths moving, “I ask of you to protect this space bounded by sigils. I ask that those within stay within. I ask that rituals that try to enter may be broken. I name you, homunculus of mine, Protector and bid that you maintain this barrier.”</p>
<p>A fire washed over them, and then moved beyond, leaving behind only the cold in its wake, expanding until it formed a bubble surrounding the apartment.</p>
<p>They opened their eyes. Ezra held its hand palm up a bit of blood coming from where it had stabbed the middle of its hand. It rose and hurried to the kitchenette to grab two paper towels. It wiped down the knife, then pressed the other one to its hand.</p>
<p>Star closed their eyes again. The spoke under their breath. “River, River, River.”</p>
<p>A moment passed. They were River again, but still Star.</p>
<p>“These wards should protect you,” Star whispered. “Stay within the bounds of the sigils and your stalker can’t bother you any longer. I will find who is doing this and convince them to end it.”</p>
<p>River whispered back in their voice. “Thank you.” A hesitation. “Silvia cares deeply for you. You shouldn’t have any fear for how things will turn out.”</p>
<p>They bit their lower lip. “Thank you.” They raised their voice. “I would like to know what you know about who’s doing this to you.”</p>
<p>“What I know about him is limited,” River said. “About a month after I died a psychic summoned me to his body with someone I didn’t recognize. But I recognized what he was talking about. He cried and apologized for the car accident that killed me.”</p>
<p>They sighed. “Which was fine, I guess. But then, he did it again the next week and the week after. There were gaps, presumably when he visited frauds, and there were different psychics who summoned me. Each new body I found myself in, he used a new name. He’s tall, red hair, and freckles and he always wears an expensive suit. I figure he must be rich. Eventually it stopped being psychics and he just started doing the seances himself. Once that happened, it started happening multiple times a week. It’s been draining to deal with.”</p>
<p>“Sounds like,” Ezra said, a paper towel held against its hand, “he’s developed an unhealthy relationship to your death. Which would be fine, if he didn’t make it your problem.”</p>
<p>River grimaced. “And it sounds like anyone with actual talent who he went to figured out what was up eventually, and he learned how to differentiate between real talents and scams.”</p>
<p>“So then,” Silvia said, “what should we do?”</p>
<p>“Find him. Force him to confront the harm he’s been doing. Make his unhealthy relationship to his grief his problem, not mine.”</p>
<p>Silvia smiled. “Sounds like a plan.”</p>
<hr>
<p>“How long will it take for me to get the copy of the accident report?”</p>
<p>Coffee infused the air of the police station. People chattered all around them and the florescent light in the ceiling flickered and buzzed. The combined sensory experience made it difficult for Star to concentrate on the woman at the desk wearing a bored expression. Silvia’s hand on their shoulder helped to keep them calm.</p>
<p>“I don’t know, sir.” They winced when she said that. “You’ll need to fill the forms out first and then I can file them and then I can say how long this will take.”</p>
<p>“Ok, ok,” they said, “I just wanted to make sure I wasn’t wasting my time before filling this out. I’ll get it ready for you in a moment.”</p>
<p>They returned to a hard backed folding chair with a clipboard and some paper on it. They filled it out slowly, staring down at it.</p>
<p>“It’ll be ok.” Silvia squeezed their shoulder. “They’re not going to do anything improper in the middle of the station.”</p>
<p>Their breathing slowed. They hadn’t realized how quick it had gotten.</p>
<p>“Yes. I just don’t have good experiences in police stations.”</p>
<p>They leaned against Silvia and filled out the rest of the form. They rose and returned to the desk, handing it to the receptionist.</p>
<p>“Let me know when this would be available.” They fixed a smile to their face. “Thank you.”</p>
<p>The lady took it and made a phone call. She asked about the file and gave some of the information on the forms, including their deadname. Then she hung up and turned back to them.</p>
<p>“I’m sorry, but the arrest report isn’t on file right now. I won’t be able to send this to you for another two months. Do you still want it?”</p>
<p>They grimaced. “No, don’t bother. Thank you anyway.”</p>
<p>They left in a hurry and regrouped at Silvia’s motorcycle where they fumbled out a cigarette with shaky hands. Silvia light it for them and they took a long drag of it, blowing their anxiety out with the smoke. Silvia gently put a hand on their back and let them calm down.</p>
<p>They took another drag of their cigarette. “It’s ok. I’ve calmed down.”</p>
<p>Silvia smiled to them. “So where should we go next?”</p>
<p>“I could ask a friend to get the files anyway, but I don’t want to do that unless I have to. I think I should just talk to the psychics who channeled River. He used a fake name, but I doubt he paid in cash.” They frowned. “I don’t expect much. Psychics usually maintain their client’s confidentiality.”</p>
<p>They donned their helmets and mounted the motorcycle. Star put their arms around Silvia’s waist.</p>
<p>“Say, Silvia,” they said. “Once this is all over, we should talk.”</p>
<p>Silence hung in the air. Silvia said, “We should.”</p>
<p>The motorcycle roared and they left the station.</p>
<hr>
<p>As Star expected, every psychic they’d seen hadn’t given them much. They said they might have had a client like that and that their clients expected them to maintain their privacy and, if someone like that was visiting them, they had recommended that he talk to someone else.</p>
<p>The last one on the list had an office in a small strip mall, flanked by a dentist and a weed shop. A small placard sat in the window that read, <i>Cezary’s Psychic Consultations</i>. A small bell jingled when they walked in.</p>
<p>A receptionist with long black hair looked up from his desk. “Hi. Welcome to Cezary’s. Do you have an appointment?”</p>
<p>Star shook their head. “I’m a colleague, not a client.” They pulled out a business card and handed it to the receptionist.</p>
<p>He read it over, then called back, “Cezary, you have a colleague here to see you.”</p>
<p>They stood there a few moments, then the door to the back opened. The person who stepped out had short greying hair on a face which had only the beginnings of wrinkles. He grinned wide.</p>
<p>“Come on in... What’re your names?”</p>
<p>“I’m Star,” they said. “This is my friend Silvia. I’m a psychic and here to talk about a client.”</p>
<p>Cezary led them in and sat them down at two chairs. “So what can I help you with?”</p>
<p>They cleared their throat. “I recently got contacted by a friend of Silvia’s who introduced me to a ghost called River. Xe told me about how someone keeps trying to get xer channeled, initially through various psychics, and eventually just doing it himself. He killed xer in a car accident and he kept apologizing to xer.”</p>
<p>Cezary frowned and looked down at his desk. “I might know something about someone like that. But I can’t speak details because of a confidentiality agreement. You understand.”</p>
<p>“Yes. I’m sorry for wasting-”</p>
<p>Cezary waved a his hand cutting them off. “I didn’t say I had nothing to provide for you.”</p>
<p>Star shut their mouth.</p>
<p>“If I had a client like that,” Cezary continued, “which maybe I did and maybe I didn’t. I would have certainly found the way he asked me to participate in his obsession uncomfortable. And I was certainly not interested in recommending another psychic for him to keep doing this. I had hoped that, if I referred him to a bookstore with resources on this sort of thing, he wouldn’t be able to tell the crap from the pearls. It seems like my hoping was misguided and I would like to extend to River my deepest apologies for whatever role I played in this.”</p>
<p>“Would you be able to tell me what bookstore you sent him to?”</p>
<p>Cezary grinned. “I certainly could.”</p>
<hr>
<p>A bell jingled and their nose was assaulted with incense. Books lined the walls of the Mystic Eye, some of them were nonsense, but Psybermagic, the Book of Thoth, and a Garden of Pomegranates, all of which were genuine, were in the mix as well. The proprietor was an woman with greying hair and a pentagram necklace dressed in a loose shirt and pleated skirt.</p>
<p>“Um, excuse me.” Star walked up to the counter. “I was wondering if I could ask you a few questions.”</p>
<p>The woman spoke with an airy voice. “I hope the spirits have kept you well. How may I help you?”</p>
<p>They let out a deep sigh. “I’m here on business. You don’t need to... Whatever. I’m a professional psychic and I’m hear on behalf of a ghost.”</p>
<p>“Oh.” The woman’s voice dropped the airy quality. “Well, uh, how can I help you, then?”</p>
<p>“I’m trying to find someone who was referred here by a colleague of mine called Cezary. He’s been harassing a ghost and I want to ask him to stop. He would’ve been in here looking for books on seances and the like.”</p>
<p>The woman bit her lower lip. “If that’s true, I’d be happy to help you. I wouldn’t want to be party to such things. But how am I to know you’re telling the truth?”</p>
<p>“What would I be able to do for you to believe me?”</p>
<p>“Show me some magic.”</p>
<p>They stepped forward to the counter. “Can you hold out your hand so I can hold it?” She complied and they took it. “Close your eyes and breath slowly.”</p>
<p>They closed their eyes as they spoke. They breathed in, and then out. There was slight movement to the air from her breath and they matched theirs with hers. They reached out and her hand fell apart into dust, but they were still holding it.</p>
<p>They breathed in and drew the dust in, and breathed out, extending out of their mouth as they did. Her whole arm crumbled and then her upper body followed. They breathed more of the dust in and extended further out as they did.</p>
<p>Soon, nothing remained before them beside dust. Their breath filled the space. They opened their eyes.</p>
<p>The woman across from them was staring. “That was amazing. I’ll get you the information you need.”</p>
<p>They left the store with a name, Teàrlach, written down on a piece of paper.</p>
<p>“Well, I hope I can get some information from this.”</p>
<hr>
<p>“Huh,” Star said, “I know one of his coworkers.”</p>
<p>They had their laptop out in their apartment and the webpage for Teàrlach’s accounting firm open.</p>
<p>Silvia put a hand on their shoulder and leaned over to look at the laptop.</p>
<p>“Who is it?”</p>
<p>“Do you remember the grave-robbery?”</p>
<p>“I do.”</p>
<p>“This guy,” Star said, “is the son of the guy who’s grave was robbed. Not the one who did it, but his golden boy.”</p>
<p>“Can you contact him?”</p>
<p>“No,” they said, “but I know who could.”</p>
<p>They pulled out their phone and quickly texted Father Aaron, <i>do u stl hve cntctt wth theo? i nd 2 tllk to 1 off hs cwrkrs nd thght he cd hlp st tht up. its 2 hlp a lst soul fnd peace.</i></p>
<p>“You never text me like that.”</p>
<p>Star grinned at her. “Yeah, well, you’re not a Catholic priest.”</p>
<p>They looked down at their phone, but Silvia put her hand on top of theirs.</p>
<p>“It’s getting late. He won’t be able to get you a meeting until tomorrow,” she said. “Earlier you said that we should talk. Now would be a good time to do that.”</p>
<p>They put down their phone and swallowed. “I said once this was all over.”</p>
<p>“I know. And I don’t think it should wait.”</p>
<p>“Yeah. Well. Um.” They felt their cheeks heating up and they took a deep breath. “Yeah, ok. We can talk now, I suppose. That works.”</p>
<p>She gave their shoulder a slight squeeze and remained silent.</p>
<p>Star cleared their throat. “It’s just that, um, we’ve been friends for a long time and I just... I don’t want to, um... Well, like, it’s just that I really like you and I don’t know what to say exactly...”</p>
<p>They looked away from her, trailing off.</p>
<p>She gently put a hand against their face and turned it to look back at her. “I know. I feel that way too.”</p>
<p>Their lips met and nothing else mattered.</p>
<p>The room crackled and static electricity leapt up from the floor. They broke the kiss. The room was crushing them, dragging them down toward nothingness.</p>
<p>A voice came to them from deep within a tunnel. “Are you ok?”</p>
<p>Then the moment passed. They took a deep breath centering their breathing.</p>
<p>And they chanted. “River. River. River.”</p>
<p>They were River.</p>
<p>“Whatever you did worked,” they said. “I felt the pull of it. It wasn’t for me, but I felt it anyway. You’ll need to talk to your friend to work some stuff out with this.”</p>
<p>“What happened?” Sylvia said. “You were on the ground and now I can’t tell which one of you is talking.”</p>
<p>They lowered their head and they were only Star.</p>
<p>“I’m sorry.” They shook their head. “I needed to make sure my charge was ok before continuing. It was time sensitive. It seems like xer stalker tried to do another seance and I took the brunt of the pull.”</p>
<p>She pulled them in for a hug. “Are you ok?”</p>
<p>They rested their head on her shoulder and put their arms around her.</p>
<p>“Never been better.”</p>
<hr>
<p>Coffee filled Star and Silvia’s noses when they walked into the cafe. The chatter of people in the shop was distracting, but was manageable.</p>
<p>Theo was sitting with a newspaper and a coffee alone at a table with two extra seats. He was dressed in a suit with slicked back black hair. He rose and grinned at them, waiving them over.</p>
<p>“I don’t know what you did, Star,” Theo said, without allowing a chance for them to speak, “but mère and Tatienne say you did us a great favor last time we spoke.”</p>
<p>Star smiled to him, then sat at one of the chairs, letting Silvia seat herself. “It’s really no problem. I was just doing my job. Which is what I’m here to talk to you about.”</p>
<p>“Ah,” Theo said. “It’s work, not pleasure. A shame given the beauty you came here with.”</p>
<p>“She wouldn’t be interested, anyway,” they said. “She’s not particularly interested in men.”</p>
<p>“What a shame. So many beauties lost that way.” He bowed his head in mock solemnity and Star winced. “Anyway, what is it that you needed to speak to me about?”</p>
<p>“I’m helping a client like I was the last time we spoke,” Star said, “and they have particular business with one of your associates, Teàrlach. I have been asked to set up a meeting with him to resolve their dispute.”</p>
<p>Theo took a long slurp from his coffee. “You talk like the assholes at HR. But you did my family a solid, so I’ll help out. I’ll arrange a meeting with him over lunch. What should I tell him you are?”</p>
<p>“Tell him that, last night, I’m the one who stopped him from seeing the one who’s life he took.”</p>
<p>Theo narrowed his eyes. “I heard about the car accident and the death, but I don’t know how you could’ve stopped him from visiting her grave.”</p>
<p>Star shrugged. “You don’t need to understand it. He will.”</p>
<p>“I’ll text that priest when and where you can meet him.”</p>
<p>Star rose and took Silvia’s hand. The two of them walked out of the coffee shop. They mounted Silvia’s motorcycle and took the short drive back to the apartment.</p>
<p>Their walk up to the apartment was blocked by a tall blonde woman leaning against the door with her arms crossed glowering at them.</p>
<p>“Looking into a car accident? Are you interested in robbing another grave?”</p>
<p>Star sighed. “Hi, Lisa. It’s always nice to meet you and your baseless accusations. I’d like to enter my home.”</p>
<p>Lisa stepped to the side raising her hands, palm facing forward. “Oh, by all means. I have no interest in stopping you. I’m just letting you know that I’m watching you. Your scams won’t go on forever.”</p>
<p>Silvia grinned at her. “Thank you so much for letting us know. We’ll have to take that into consideration. Have a wonderful day.”</p>
<p>They entered the apartment together.</p>
<p>When they crossed the threshold, they were River.</p>
<p>“So how did it go?”</p>
<p>Silvia stared a second, then said, “Oh, River. It went well. The guy we met with owes Star, so he’s setting up a meeting over lunch.”</p>
<p>River hesitated, then spoke. “I’ll admit, I’m nervous about this. But I don’t think that Star could get him off without me there.”</p>
<p>Silvia put a hand on their shoulder. “It’ll be ok, River. If you don’t want to go, you don’t have to. But this isn’t Star’s first time doing this and I’ll be there with you.”</p>
<p>They took a deep breath, slowing their heart rate. “I trust you, Silvia. So I trust Star.”</p>
<p>They were only Star once more.</p>
<hr>
<p>Star wrinkled their nose at the smell of steak as they entered the restaurant. Tacky paintings covered the walls illuminated by cheap florescent lights, humming softly as background noise.</p>
<p>“I really wish,” Star said, “Theo would stop setting up meetings for me here.”</p>
<p>“I’m not sure he cares if you don’t like it here.”</p>
<p>A hostess greeted them and directed them to their table.</p>
<p>Cologne overwhelmed them as they approached a table with a broad shouldered man with short cropped red hair, messy and uncombed sitting there. He had bags around his light eyes. He wore a messy, but expensive, black suit with a loosely tied red tie. He stood with a frown and extended his hand to them.</p>
<p>Star and Silvia sat at the table and he had to drop his extended hand.</p>
<p>“So,” Teàrlach said, “why has Theo told me I must meet with the two of you?”</p>
<p>Star met his eyes, briefly, then looked down and to the side. They cleared their throat. “I’m here on behalf of River to mediate the growing problem between the two of you.”</p>
<p>His mouth opened, then closed. He looked down at his food, a steak, for a moment. “Are you here to give me absolution?”</p>
<p>Star shook their head. “I don’t think I could even if I wanted to. You need to figure that out yourself. I’m here to ask you to stop summoning xer. It’s making xer incredibly uncomfortable. When I saw xer, I was operating on xer request, and, yet, xe began the meeting with a panic about if I was you summoning xer again.”</p>
<p>Teàrlach put his fork down, but not his knife. “I don’t know what I’ve done wrong, here. I’ve only sought... What was it you referred to River with? Xer?” Star nodded. “I’ve only sought xer out to make amends for what I’ve done to xer.”</p>
<p>“Have you considered,” Silvia cut in, “that xe might not care about you making amends? All you’re doing is making your problems xer problems.”</p>
<p>“And who,” Teàrlach said, pointing to Silvia, “are you?”</p>
<p>“I’m a friend of River’s. I got them,” Silvia pointed to Star with her thumb, “on this job.”</p>
<p>“And what gives the two of you some special insight into what xe wants?”</p>
<p>“I’ve spoken with xer,” Star said. “Xe asked for this.”</p>
<p>Teàrlach took a bite of his steak and took his time eating it. He shook his head. “I don’t believe you. One of the psychic freaks who got annoyed with me put you up to it. All I’ve done is make amends.”</p>
<p>“All you’ve done,” Silvia snapped, “is be an ass-”</p>
<p>Star cut in. “River. River. River.”</p>
<p>They were River.</p>
<p>Teàrlach creased his brow, “What’s that supposed-”</p>
<p>River said, “They are telling the truth.”</p>
<p>Teàrlach’s mouth hung open.</p>
<p>“I don’t want you to try to contact me ever again.”</p>
<p>“I’m so sorry.” He bowed his head. “I never meant to hit you like I did.”</p>
<p>River scoffed. “Ugh. Even when I’m telling you quite directly, you don’t get it.”</p>
<p>They were only Star, again.</p>
<p>“I know,” he said. “I can’t understand your pain. I can only understand how I hurt you. How I should’ve been more careful.”</p>
<p>Star cleared their throat. “Xe left already.”</p>
<p>“I wish xe hadn’t,” he said. “I wish I could’ve done more to make amends before xe left.”</p>
<p>“If you want to make amends,” Star said, “then the first step is to stop continuing to inflict harm upon xer.”</p>
<p>“I’m not inflicting harm,” he snapped. “All I’ve been doing is say I’m sorry.”</p>
<p>“You are stalking xer.” Star glared at him. “Xe exists in fear of you. You killed xer, yes, and now you are making xer life after death into hell.”</p>
<p>Teàrlach stared at his food for several moments. “Why?” he said. “I thought this was what I was supposed to do with my guilt. To seek absolution from those I harmed. To get forgiveness. I’ve already seen priests about this, but none of them could give me the absolution I needed.”</p>
<p>Star reached out and put a hand on his, the dark of their skin contrasted with the pale of Teàrlach’s. “You don’t need someone else to forgive you for this. If you had, the first priest you saw would’ve been enough or the first time you spoke to River would’ve been enough. It is neither your god nor River’s spirit who have failed to forgive you. And they don’t need to.”</p>
<p>“Then who does need to?”</p>
<p>Star hesitated. “The harm you did to River isn’t about you. Xe has no need to forgive you because it’s xer harm, not yours. Xe only has an obligation to xerself to treat xerself fairly and with kindness. To find peace in xer death and to figure out how to move on.” They paused a moment. Teàrlach remained silent. “You don’t need xer forgiveness, either. The problem you have is that you haven’t forgiven yourself. And you’ve spent all the time since making that everyone else’s problem.”</p>
<p>“How could I possibly do that?” Teàrlach said. “How could I possibly forgive myself?”</p>
<p>“I don’t know,” they said. “I can’t answer that question for you. This is something you need to work through for yourself.” They paused a moment. “I do think you’d probably benefit from seeing a therapist about this. It’s not a silver bullet to resolving your problems, but you can afford it and it’ll do you more help than stalking River.”</p>
<p>He frowned. “Ok. I can see a therapist.”</p>
<p>“You won’t be able to talk with River again,” they said. “I’m perfectly capable of stopping anyone from being able to contact xer. I will be able to tell if you try.”</p>
<p>He swallowed. “I won’t try.”</p>
<p>Star smiled at him. “I do hope you can get the help you need.”</p>
<p>They rose alongside Silvia and took her hand. The two walked out of the restaurant together.</p>
<hr>
<p class="align-center">If you enjoy these stories, please consider pledging monthly money to my <a href="https://www.patreon.com/deathpigeon">Patreon</a> or one time donations with <a href="https://venmo.com/Zara-Storm">Venmo</a> or <a href="https://cash.app/$deathpigeon">Cashapp</a>. Thank you.</p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/ghost-crimes/">Read more Ghost Crimes.</a></p>
<p class="align-center">Previous: THE FIRE WITH NO NAME</p>
<p class="align-center">Next: OUT SEPTEMBER 1ST</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Auto(mated) Theft</title>
        <author>
            <name>Zara RW Storm</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/automated-theft/"/>
        <id>https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/automated-theft/</id>
            <category term="Auto(mated) Theft"/>

        <updated>2021-09-06T21:22:17-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    In the near future in Siberia, coal mining has been completely automated, including shipping which is done by self-driving trucks filled with coal, destroying local ecosystems and communities, who see none of the benefits. These automated systems are exploited by a team of bandit-hackers to&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p class="align-center">In the near future in Siberia, coal mining has been completely automated, including shipping which is done by self-driving trucks filled with coal, destroying local ecosystems and communities, who see none of the benefits.</p>
<p class="align-center">These automated systems are exploited by a team of bandit-hackers to hijack the trucks and steal the coal as the company takes measures to stop them.</p>
<p class="align-center">It's a war in Siberia between bandit-hackers and a coal company.</p>
<h2 class="align-center">Auto(mated) Theft!</h2>
<h4>Arc 1:</h4>
<p>Part 1: OUT FEBRUARY 1ST 2022!</p>
<p>Part 2: OUT AUGUST 1ST 2022!</p>
<p>Part 3: OUT FEBRUARY 1ST 2023!</p>
<p>Part 4: OUT AUGUST 1ST 2023!</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Fire With No Name (Ghost Crimes #3)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Zara RW Storm</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/the-fire-with-no-name-ghost-crimes-3/"/>
        <id>https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/the-fire-with-no-name-ghost-crimes-3/</id>
            <category term="Ghost Crimes"/>

        <updated>2021-09-06T21:22:17-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Content Warning: Destructive Rain Storm, Destruction of Possessions and Home, Discussions of Heavy Topics, Irreality, Hallucinations, Psychedelia, Spirit Possession Ezra loomed over where Star sat on the floor of their apartment. “You might be a natural at spirit channeling,” it said, “but you’ve never developed&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p class="align-center">Content Warning: Destructive Rain Storm, Destruction of Possessions and Home, Discussions of Heavy Topics, Irreality, Hallucinations, Psychedelia, Spirit Possession</p>
<hr>
<p>Ezra loomed over where Star sat on the floor of their apartment.</p>
<p>“You might be a natural at spirit channeling,” it said, “but you’ve never developed your magical talent in any serious way. That’s why basics like this are necessary.”</p>
<p>Star stared at their feet. <i>N</i><i>o use complaining,</i> they thought. Ezra might look like a hot topic disaster, but it knew what it was talking about.</p>
<p>“I understand that,” they said. “I just can’t hold my gaze like that.”</p>
<p>Ezra ran a pale hand through its bleached blond hair. It was tall and thin, dressed in all black with black nails and lips to match. “I know. But that’s not a reason to give up. If this was easy, everyone would do it. But enough practice can conquer any barrier.” It smiled. “Mastering object concentration is important to developing your magical talent. It creates avenues for power to flow and allows you to unlock secrets contained within the objects you concentrate on.”</p>
<p>Star nodded and looked across their room again. The wall was featureless, but Ezra had put a blue dot on the wall. They held their gaze, unwavering.</p>
<p>Then Ezra’s phone rung.</p>
<p>“Shit, sorry.” Ezra fumbled with its phone. “I need to take this.”</p>
<p>It strode out the door in a few steps while it flipped open its phone. Before it closed the door behind it they heard, “Hi, dad.”</p>
<p>They returned their gaze to the dot. They fought with their eyes to keep them fixed on it. The wall around it blurred and the dot came into greater focus. Despite the distance, the texture of it came into focus. The upper left part of it was coming off the wall slightly. The dot wasn’t perfectly smooth. They struggled to make out the exact features of it as they formed a singular texture, a unitary whole.</p>
<p>The door creaked open. They struggled to keep their gaze on the dot and not look to the door. A few moments pass and the dot remained in their vision.</p>
<p>Then it fell to the side.</p>
<p>“See? You’re doing much better already.” Ezra put a hand on their shoulder. “More practice and you could’ve held the gaze while I got the call, left the room, and came back.”</p>
<p>“It provides a sort of clarity,” they said. “The intense focus lets me see things I would’ve missed on a casual inspection.”</p>
<p>Ezra grinned. “Enough time and you can see more than you could ever imagine.”</p>
<p>Star smiled. “So what did your dad have to say?”</p>
<p>“Oh.” Ezra’s demeanor collapsed. “Well, uh... I was hoping to ask you about that. Because, well, uh, he asked a favor and I’m not sure I’m equipped for it, and I told him that, but he trusts me, and that’s sweet and all but I really don’t know what I’m doing with a lot of spirit work, and certainly don’t have a lot of field experience, I’ve always focused on different things. And, well, like, I told him that maybe I could ask someone else to help and he insisted I at least come along and...”</p>
<p>It stopped and took a few deep breaths.</p>
<p>“I guess what I’m saying,” it said, “is I think I got you a job with my dad, if you’re willing to help.”</p>
<p>Star nodded. “I’ll see what I can do.”</p>
<hr>
<p>The stench of cow shit greeted them at the house with a blast of wet air from the north east. The leaves of a tall oak tree rippled, partly obscuring distant dark clouds to the north east. In the shadow of the oak tree was a ramshackle house. The lawn was overgrown and the facade of the house beaten up.</p>
<p>In the yard a weathered man was picking up metal pieces off of the ground. He wore a denim jacket with several patches showing off bands Star had never heard of.</p>
<p>Ezra said, “Hi, dad.”</p>
<p>The man stood and turned. His skin was wrinkled and his black nail polish was chipped.</p>
<p>“Oh, hi, Ezra,” He extended a hand in Star’s direction. “And you must be its friend. I’m Arnie, its father.”</p>
<p>Star took his hand and shook it. “It’s a pleasure to meet you, Arnie. I’m Star, a medium.”</p>
<p>“Well met.” He grinned. “You might be able to help me with the weird shit I’ve been dealing with.”</p>
<p>He gestured to pieces of metal chain that were strewn across the yard.</p>
<p>“Chainsaw broke?”</p>
<p>Arnie frowned. “While I was cutting the tree. It’s an old tree and it’s hard to maintain. The HOA is on my ass about it. It’s easier to just cut it down.”</p>
<p>His back straightened and his frown turned to a slight smile. “What I wasn’t saying is that weird shit has been happening since I started working on the tree. Branches scratching against windows, things being moved while I slept, and so on and so forth.”</p>
<p>“Sounds like you upset some sort of spirit,” Star said. “Your kid came to the right person to deal with the issue.”</p>
<p>They stepped toward the tree and looked toward Arnie. “I’m going touch your tree and try to see if anything is there. Probably there’ll be no visible change, but I don’t want to do it without your permission, first.”</p>
<p>Arnie nodded and gestured for them to continue, the frown returning to his face. Star pressed their palm against the tree and close their eyes.</p>
<p>The physicality of the bark pressed against them, the roughness of the bumps and divets. They stopped all movement beyond steady breathing, keeping their hand in the same place. The bark had a hole the shape of a beak. It was cracked and broken apart. And the energy of it flowed like water up and down the trunk and into their hand, bringing a warmth with it. The energy had its own bumps and divets. Places where growth hadn’t been as good as it could’ve been. Scars from previous trauma. And a swirl far above them in the top of the branches.</p>
<p>The flow of the warmth increased, filling their hand hand more, becoming scalding. They pulled their hand away and shook it a bit.</p>
<p>Arnie frowned. “So there’s something in there?”</p>
<p>“Yes,” they said. “And not something that liked me poking around.”</p>
<p>“So what are you going to do?” Arnie smiled. “I just want some peace in the house.”</p>
<p>Star looked to Ezra and mouthed, ‘I’m sorry.’</p>
<p>They turned back to Arnie. “I think I’m going to need to stay the night to see what the spirit does.”</p>
<p>Arnie nodded. “The two of you can get Ezra’s old room.”</p>
<p>Ezra groaned and glared at Star.</p>
<p>Arnie led the two of them into the house, it was quiet and odorless inside, through a small front room and into a kitchen separated from a living room by a counter. Dishes were piled up in the sink, but the counters were clean. The living room had a simple couch, a record player between two filled bookshelves, and a table with simple chairs around it.</p>
<p>“There’s only one room the two of you could stay in upstairs.” Arnie pointed toward the narrow stairs to the left of the entrance of the living room. “I never figured out what to do with Ezra’s room when it moved out.”</p>
<p>Ezra led them up the stairs into a cramped upstairs with two rooms, one on each end of a hallway. Its room had a single bed, a comfortable office chair, and a bare desk.</p>
<p>“Not much room.” It sat on its bed. “My dad’s never really been all that rich, so this is the best house we could ever get. And it doesn’t have my stuff in it anymore.”</p>
<p>“That’s ok,” Star said. “I wasn’t planning on getting much sleep tonight, anyway. Tonight is when I get started on my work.”</p>
<p>Ezra sighed. “I guess I wasn’t going to get much sleep tonight, either. What’s the plan?”</p>
<p>“We wait for your dad to fall asleep, that’s when it sounds like the spirit is the most active,” they said, “then we go follow the noise and see what’s going on and what we need to do to communicate with whoever is doing this.”</p>
<p>“And if talking to it doesn’t work?”</p>
<p>“Well,” they said, “I’m not exactly an expert on restraining spirits, yet, despite my training with you. So I guess that part is as much on you as it is on me.”</p>
<p>Ezra sighed. “Please don’t fuck this up, ok? I love my dad. His life has been hard enough as it is. Poverty, multiple stints in mental institutions, raising me as a single parent. I don’t want him to have to deal with more than he has to.”</p>
<p>“I will do what I can.” They put a hand on its shoulder. “I can’t promise we can get him a perfect outcome, but I can promise that I’ll be his advocate with the spirits as best I can.”</p>
<p>Ezra smiled. “Thanks.”</p>
<p>Ezra unpacked a bag of its tools. Various rods and crystals and cloth with sigils on them. Star left its room to allow it to deal with the tools and headed downstairs.</p>
<p>The house had a sort of stillness. There wasn't any particular smell nor any sound. The air flowed only slightly and the energy of the space moved much like the air. There was a sort of stability to its movement.</p>
<p>They sat in the middle of the living room and closed their eyes to meditate.</p>
<p>They reached for the movement of the energy in the room, again. The stability came into focus. The energy moved in two ways, a double spiral through the house. The two flows of energy were dancers moving with in sync. Arnie’s energy infused into the space, giving it structure.</p>
<p>Beneath the spirals, another energy moved, rolling like a wave. Where it passed through, the spirals were disrupted and the wave broken. Where the spirals moved in harmony, the wave moved discordantly with them. Not strong enough to break the stability, but its power was growing.</p>
<p>Star focused on the wave like the dot on the wall. Everything else melted away. The aroma of grass and trees after a storm overwhelmed them, the sound of wind passing through leaves effused the space. The spirals were distant, nonsensical. An order imposing itself on an already ordered space.</p>
<p>The wave swelled and fell. Anger and pain flowed through it, brilliant orange and red fire drawing lines across it. The wave flowed from the tree moving through the grass, passing into other trees and spaces, running into other barriers, worse so than the spirals.</p>
<p>The chime of music came from behind them while the fragrance of oregano wafted through the air. They opened their eyes. Color drained from the world. Everything appeared dull and distant, as if the space didn't exist. They stood, their joints cracking.</p>
<p>“Ah.” A voice echoed from miles away. “You’re back.”</p>
<p>The world blurred and sounds became distant. All that remained was their grip on the bookshelf. Buzzing filled their head.</p>
<p>Everything cleared up and they were on the floor. Ezra was running toward them.</p>
<p>“I’m ok.” Their voice slurred as they spoke. “That was just really intense. Give me a moment.”</p>
<p>Ezra helped them up and into a chair.</p>
<p>“Dad made pasta,” it said. “I’ll get you a plate.”</p>
<p>Star nodded. “Thanks.”</p>
<p>Ezra brought them pasta with a red sauce and cheese. It and Arnie sat at the table. The sauce was chunky and filled with veggies. With each bite, color returned to the world.</p>
<p>Arnie put down his fork, finished with his plate. The smile on his face aligned with the clockwise spiral in the house.</p>
<p>“So,” he said, “what was that about?”</p>
<p>Star swallowed. “I was getting a feel for the energy of the space. I went too deep and it was overwhelming. I was left everything feeling dull when I came back.”</p>
<p>“Was that what’s causing the issue?”</p>
<p>“It was the energy of the tree,” they said. “It was was like waves in a pool after someone big jumps in. The spirit’s energy flowed through it like lines of fire.”</p>
<p>Ezra said, “Is it powerful?”</p>
<p>Star nodded. “It doesn’t change what needs to be done. It just lets me know what it is whoever is doing this is like.”</p>
<p>Arnie got up and got a second plate of pasta. Star savored every bite of theirs.</p>
<p>“It was beautiful,” they said. “Or maybe sublime is the right word. It was like looking down from the peak of a mountain and seeing the whole of the world laid out before you.”</p>
<p>Ezra and Arnie stared at them and they smiled back. Arnie frowned, taking on the energy of the counterclockwise spiral, and returned to his food. The rest of the meal continued in silence.</p>
<p>At the meal’s end, Ezra collected the plates and took them to the kitchen and the now empty sinks and washed them. Arnie excused himself from the table after a brief chat.</p>
<p>“It’s late and I should start getting to sleep.”</p>
<p>He left up the stairs to his room and Ezra came to join Star.</p>
<p>“So this spirit will do its work while dad’s asleep?”</p>
<p>Star nodded. “Your dad’s energy pervades this space and gives it an order the spirit is less capable of effecting. But he’ll have less control of it and less power behind it when he’s asleep. So it’s the perfect time for the spirit to act. For now, though, we should return to your room and wait for anything to happen.”</p>
<hr>
<p>Wind picked up outside of Ezra’s window. The wooden fence around the property rattled. Star closed their eyes centering themself. The wave grew in the absence of the double helix, a tide rising against the house. They bolted to the door.</p>
<p>The air was pierced by a horrendous scraping of wood against glass then a crash downstairs. They turned back to face Ezra.</p>
<p>“Come on.” They motioned forward. “It’s time for our work to begin.”</p>
<p>They hurried down the stairs, the footsteps of Ezra behind them. A blast of cold air met them at the bottom. Their nose was assaulted with a mixture of cow manure and freshly rained on grass. Glass was scattered around the floor, the window in the kitchen was shattered inward. Pots and pans were flipped.</p>
<p>They stepped into the kitchen. The air around them swirled. They closed their eyes and reached out to it. They were underwater. Everywhere around them was the energy from the wave. Color filled their vision, a brilliant red and orange, anger and hate. Something reached back to them. A familiar heat touched them and they yelped and withdrew. The wind blew past them and up the stairs. A door slammed. Arnie screamed.</p>
<p>Ezra winced. “Shit, shit.”</p>
<p>It scrambled up the stairs and Star scrambled after it. The door to Arnie’s room was torn off its hinges. Another blast of air hit them from inside the room. Arnie lay on the floor coughing and sobbing. Behind him his window was shattered outward. Papers were scattered on the floor.</p>
<p>Ezra knelt by its father. It looked up. “This needs to end.”</p>
<p>Star nodded. “Stay with him.”</p>
<p>They turned and marched down the stairs and out the door. Mud splashed against their legs and rain soaked their hair. They stared up at the massive tree as they approached.</p>
<p>They reached out and touched it like they did before. They closed their eyes and breathed. The physicality of the tree filled them. The heat was there, again, and they avoided it for now. They felt every nook and cranny of the bark, every capillary of the trunk, every movement of the branches. They were the tree.</p>
<p>They couldn’t see, couldn’t hear, couldn’t smell. The wind rustled through them and rain rolled off of their leaves. They reached deep into the ground, their roots surrounded by mycelia of countless fungi fed them. They reached far to each side, scraping against a tilted structure beneath their canopy.</p>
<p>They had been a sapling here initially, so many leaf falls ago. This was their home. It had been through the presence of many humans.</p>
<p>A fire filled their capillaries, but did not burn. They shared their space effortlessly. Their space was for sharing. For the squirrels to make their homes, for the birds to make their nests.</p>
<p>The fire had no name, but they knew nem. They were nir home.</p>
<p>The fire with no name echoed through the whole of the tree. “Who are you?”</p>
<p>“I am a medium,” Star said. “I wish you no harm. I merely wish to speak with you.”</p>
<p>Heat lashed out at them and they gritted their teeth.</p>
<p>“I haven’t harmed you, fire.” They struggled to hold their voice steady. “You have reacted to every attempt to reach out to you with hostility and violence.”</p>
<p>The heat retreated. “You may not have, but your kind has. Was it not your kind who destroyed our forests? Was it not your kind who paved our ground? All for your profit.”</p>
<p>Star shook their head. “It may have been humans who did that, but not all humans were involved in that. Your forests were destroyed by those who live here for profit. My people were torn from our homes and taken here in chains for that same profit.”</p>
<p>“But you speak for the human in the house,” ne said. “You help one who seeks to destroy yet another of my homes.”</p>
<p>“I am a conduit between your kind and his. You can speak through me as much as he can.”</p>
<p>The fire with no name swirled through the trunk. “Why would you speak on my behalf?”</p>
<p>“It is what I do. I give the injuries of the past a voice. If you come with me, I will give you a voice. I will let you speak. You can tell the human in the house how he has hurt you.”</p>
<p>“And why should I believe you?”</p>
<p>Star lowered their defenses and let go. Their memories and thoughts poured into the tree.</p>
<p>It was middle school. They met their first spirit and she told them that she had been hurt and abused. They listened to her and, then, let her enter their body. She told the bullies who had hurt her what they had done wrong. They had been beaten for it. The spirit moved on and they had cried in the bathroom. The bullies had never left them alone.</p>
<p>It was freshman year of high school. A boy who had been killed for being gay spoke to them. He had died decades ago, but he still missed the one boy who was kind to him, even if he never loved him back. They looked him up and tracked him down. He worked fast food. The boy never worked up the courage to ask Star to speak to him, so they hadn’t.</p>
<p>It was graduation day. A spirit cried in a stream outside of their high school. A housing development was going to be built over the summer and the spirit’s home was going to be radically transformed and zie couldn’t handle it. They sat with the spirit and talked with hir all day helping hir calm down. They never went to their graduation, but their regret was that they were powerless to stop the construction. They slept by the stream with only the spirit to keep them company. They hadn’t been home in over a year.</p>
<p>It was two years later. A spirit was hidden in the backroom of the grocery store. They spoke with her every day while they stocked shelves. She didn’t remember how she died, but she appreciated the company. One day she asked them to help her move on. It took them three weeks to set up, but they finally performed a séance for her in the homeless encampment where they slept. They missed her after she was gone.</p>
<p>It was four years after that. A spirit spoke to them while they were taking someone’s order at the fast food joint they worked at. The man who was ordering had stalked her for years before she had committed suicide. They let her take them over and she punched him in the face. They spent the night in jail and they worried over how they’d make rent without that job.</p>
<p>It was five years more. They spoke with their first client at their job as a psychic. Her cat had died. They let her speak to her one last time. She lived in a rundown apartment and they refused to let her pay them their full rate for what they had finished. They’d lived like that.</p>
<p>It was five months ago. They were invited over to a house where an exorcism had taken place, a ghost was murdered.</p>
<p>It was three months ago. The ghost of a father asked them to find who robbed their grave before the police so his children wouldn’t go to jail.</p>
<p>It was two weeks ago. They helped a ghost visit his lover one last time before moving on.</p>
<p>It was this morning. Their friend’s father had asked for help. He struggled with his life and his child was all he had left.</p>
<p>It was this afternoon. They had promised their friend that they would be its father’s advocate whatever happened, but they had touched the wave of energy, they had felt its beauty. They would make a liar of themself.</p>
<p>It was this night. They had come out to end the conflict. They submitted themself to the mercy of the fire with no name.</p>
<p>The fire with no name had filled up their body. Like the tree, ne did not burn them.</p>
<p>Ne said, “You are not what I thought you were. I believe you.”</p>
<p>Star collapsed to their knees panting. They took a moment to compose themself.</p>
<p>“I’ll be your advocate with the human in the house.” They stood. “I promise you that I am on your side.”</p>
<p>With fire in their veins, Star turned from the tree and walked back to the house.</p>
<hr>
<p>Arnie and Ezra sat on the couch in the living room. Ezra had an arm around its father and was talking softly to him. It looked up at Star.</p>
<p>“Have you dealt with-”</p>
<p>Star cut it off. “We need to talk. All four of us.”</p>
<p>They moved in front of the couch and sat cross legged.</p>
<p>Ezra stared in shock. “You brought that thing back with you?”</p>
<p>Star nodded slowly. “The fire with no name has grievances and it would be irresponsible to banish nem without talking.”</p>
<p>Ezra opened its mouth again, its brow furrowed, but Star locked eyes with it. They held their gaze as they did upon the dot in their room. As Ezra’s mouth moved, no sound came out. Its eyes widened, a brilliant green. There were flecks of silver in them. They darted around the room, the eyes moving frantically. The whole world slowed and narrowed and it was only the eyes. They came back returning the stare.</p>
<p>A needle stabbed into Star’s eye, cold, dark, and rigid. Pain exploded outward from and they struggled to hold firm. The cold faded, and then burned. The heat in their veins taking it over. A flash of orange, green, and blue covered the distance between Star and Ezra.</p>
<p>Ezra flinched and a hand went to its eyes. Arnie looked to Ezra.</p>
<p>“What just happened?”</p>
<p>Ezra stood and left the room. Star looked to Arnie.</p>
<p>“It’s not important right now. I’ll deal with the consequences later. There is someone you need to talk to face to face.”</p>
<p>“You mean whatever it is that’s been doing this to me?”</p>
<p>Heat flared through them. Their name burned away. Their back hunched and their shoulders collapsed inward as they moved their hands in front of their face, baring claws they didn’t have.</p>
<p>They coughed several times. Their voice was frail and gravelly. “You need to talk to me.” Silence fell and they looked up, their eyes wide. “It is my home you are attempting to take down after all.”</p>
<p>Arnie frowned. “Your home?”</p>
<p>“The tree,” they snapped. “It is where I live. I have lost too many homes. I am not going to lose another.”</p>
<p>Arnie nodded. “I understand. I have lost many homes myself. This house is the longest I’ve ever lived in any one place. Twelve years. Before that, I lost many homes. I’ve been evicted, I’ve had homes destroyed. But I don’t know what I’m supposed to do. The HOA says I have to do more maintenance on the tree or cut it down, and I can’t climb the tree nor can I afford for someone else to do the maintenance for me.”</p>
<p>They let out a low rumbling from their throat. “Why is it that they are able to control what you do with your own home? Ignore them.”</p>
<p>“I wish I could. But they can levy fines against me. They already don’t like me because I’m bad at maintaining my yard.” He stared down at his hands. “I could lose my home if I don’t do what they say.”</p>
<p>“Then we both are in danger of losing our homes.” They looked up at Arnie. “So what are we going to do about it?”</p>
<p>“If I had the money I could get someone to do some maintenance on the tree. Cut dead branches and such. Or someone could help me do it. But I can barely afford the mortgage on the house. Nor do I have friends to turn to for this. The best I have is Ezra.” Arnie motioned upstairs. “But it isn’t much better at that sort of manual labor than I am.”</p>
<p>“Dead branches? That’s the problem?”</p>
<p>Arnie nodded. “It’s ‘unsightly’, apparently.”</p>
<p>Ne considered the issue. Nir power wasn’t exactly fit for the job. Ne worked with natural processes, the wind, the movement of the tree, and those were either incapable of dealing with dead branches, trees couldn’t exactly drop them on their own initiative, or too much of a blunt instrument, the wind wouldn’t be able to destroy only the dead branches. Nor would the vessel ne currently inhabited help. It lacked the strength to do it.</p>
<p><i>But,</i> Star thought, <i>maybe I know those who could help.</i> Memories of Silvia, their friend and a bartender. She was stronger than they were. And she might have friends to help as well.</p>
<p>Ne considered this. <i>What would it take to get her to help?</i></p>
<p>A smile spread on their face. <i>She’d probably help if I asked.</i></p>
<p>They straightened their back and dropped their hands to their sides. “The spirit isn’t able to help with that, but I might be able to.”</p>
<p>Arnie made a terse smile. “I’m not interested in charity.”</p>
<p>They shook their head. “Not charity. I know people who can help. My friend Silvia has the muscle to do this, and my brother John could get us some equipment.”</p>
<p>“And they’d do that for me?”</p>
<p>Star shrugged. “You can pay them back by helping them in the future.”</p>
<p>“And what about the windows that got shattered?”</p>
<p>Star smiled. “Well, me and Ezra have a mutual friend who could procure you some replacements, no charge.”</p>
<p>Arnie opened his mouth, then closed it again and frowned.</p>
<p>“Would this plan work for you?”</p>
<p>Arnie nodded slowly. “I’ll admit, it isn’t what I expected from your help, if I’m being honest. I thought you’d do some weird exorcism, not get me to talk with the spirit and offer me help with the tree.”</p>
<p>“I need to talk with Ezra and wrap things up with the spirit.”</p>
<hr>
<p>The fire with no name returned to nir tree with no trouble. Star had ascended the stairs to Ezra’s room. It sat on its bed facing the window. They stood in the entrance waiting for it to talk. The silence hung in the air for several minutes.</p>
<p>“Well,” it said, “what do you want?”</p>
<p>“I just want to talk.”</p>
<p>It turned to face them. “About how you promised me you’d be my father’s advocate, then turned around and became the spirit’s advocate?”</p>
<p>They nodded. “I shouldn’t have made that promise. I knew it was a mistake as soon as I touched the energy of the spirit.”</p>
<p>“What was so special about its energy?”</p>
<p>Star held out a hand. “I don’t think I could put it into words. But I could show you.”</p>
<p>Ezra hesitated then took their hand.</p>
<p>“Uh, we’re going to need to sit and I’m covered in mud and rain, so I’d prefer not to sit on your bed.”</p>
<p>The two of them situated themselves on the floor crosslegged holding each others hands. They breathed in and out together.</p>
<p>Ezra was cold, dark, and rigid. It prickled to the touch, like a thousand needles. They could only imagine how their own energy felt to it. Their breathing slowed together. Their heartbeats synchronized.</p>
<p>The spiral dominated the area around them. The cold, dark needles flowed with it.</p>
<p><i>My dad’s energy...</i></p>
<p>Star hadn’t realized they’d be able to communicate like that.</p>
<p><i>Yes,</i> they thought, <i>it’s beautiful. Two flows working harmoniously.</i></p>
<p><i>That would make sense. There are two of him. In his head, I mean.</i></p>
<p>Star nodded. <i>His energy orders this space, but it’s not the only energy in this space. We need to go down.</i></p>
<p>They reached down below the spiral, but they didn’t need to go so far. The wave moved along the spiral, rising into the house. No longer did it break against it. They sunk beneath it. Fire moved through it, like veins through an arm. It glowed in brilliant color. Green, blue, yellow, red, orange, white, and black, all overlapping and mixing, no longer a limited palette.</p>
<p><i>Go ahead,</i> they thought. <i>Touch the fire.</i></p>
<p>A spike reached toward it then hesitated a moment. It gingerly brushed against it. Star reached down and touched it as well.</p>
<p>The wind blew across the land from the northeast. The fire with no name was the wind. Grass in the whole neighborhood, some immaculately maintained, some old and overgrown, pushed upward toward where the sun would be. The fire with no name was the grass. Mourning doves slept in the branches of the tree. The tree a home for them, too. The fire with no name was the birds. The massive oak stretched to the heavens. It had existed since time immemorial. It was a world unto itself. The fire with no name was the tree.</p>
<p>They moved along the wind, hopping from breeze to breeze, twisting and spiraling through the air. Laughter filled them.</p>
<p><i>Laughter,</i> Ezra thought, <i>is the highest emotion, containing its own opposite.</i></p>
<p>Both of them laughed, their concentration broken. Star opened their eyes. The world was washed out and dull. They closed their eyes again and controlled their breathing, holding themself there for several moments before opening them again. Color was already seeping into the room.</p>
<p>Ezra stared at them.</p>
<p>Star grinned. “Ne’s beautiful.”</p>
<p>“They flowed into dad’s energy.”</p>
<p>“They didn’t last night. They clashed with each other. An irreconcilable difference, a refusal to communicate.”</p>
<p>Ezra nodded. “And so they needed to talk.”</p>
<p>“Exactly,” they said. “And your dad could speak perfectly well himself, but the tree and the fire with no name could not. So I had to be their voice.”</p>
<p>They sat in silence for awhile. Ezra broke the silence. “That’s why you do this. They don’t have a voice, but you can give them one.”</p>
<p>Star nodded. “It’s what I’ve always done.”</p>
<hr>
<p class="align-center">If you enjoy these stories, please consider pledging monthly money to my <a href="https://www.patreon.com/deathpigeon">Patreon</a> or one time donations with <a href="https://venmo.com/Zara-Storm">Venmo</a> or <a href="https://cash.app/$deathpigeon">Cashapp</a>. Thank you.</p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/ghost-crimes/">Read more Ghost Crimes.</a></p>
<p class="align-center">Previous: <a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/taken-to-the-grave-ghost-crimes-2/">TAKEN TO THE GRAVE</a></p>
<p class="align-center">Next: <a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/unforgiven/">UNFORGIVEN</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Anniversary (Ghost Crimes)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Zara RW Storm</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/anniversary/"/>
        <id>https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/anniversary/</id>
            <category term="Ghost Crimes"/>

        <updated>2021-09-06T21:22:17-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Content Warning: Transphobia, Implied Homophobia, Death, Grief, Loss, Spirit Possession Despite nearly half a year of experience as a medium, Star still didn’t know how to handle a sobbing client. The client, Akio, would look intimidating with his muscular build, harsh eyes, and pure black&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p class="align-center">Content Warning: Transphobia, Implied Homophobia, Death, Grief, Loss, Spirit Possession</p>
<hr>
<p>Despite nearly half a year of experience as a medium, Star still didn’t know how to handle a sobbing client. The client, Akio, would look intimidating with his muscular build, harsh eyes, and pure black suit, if he hadn’t collapsed against Star as soon as they were alone.</p>
<p>They patted his back gently. “There, there.”</p>
<p>“I just miss him so much...” Akio’s voice trailed off.</p>
<p>“What can I do to help?”</p>
<p>Akio took some time to compose himself. He wiped the tears from his eyes and sat down in one of the chairs in his office.</p>
<p>“I just want to talk with Mścisław again...” He took a deep breath. “It’s been hard mourning him when his family didn’t even let me to attend his funeral, and it was all conducted under his deadname anyway.”</p>
<p>They nodded slowly. “I can see what I can do to contact him.”</p>
<p>Akio smiled, drawing the wrinkles on his face into sharper contrast. “I can afford to pay you whatever you want for this. I can afford it.”</p>
<p>Star pulled some candles, a lighter, and a meditation mat with sigils drawn on it out of their bag. They laid the mat on the floor and arranged the candles around them.</p>
<p>“I’ll be sitting on this mat in the middle of the sigils chanting his name,” they said.</p>
<p>“While I do that, I’d like you to light each of these candles counterclockwise. Can you do that for me?”</p>
<p>Akio nodded. They smiled at him and then settled onto the mat and closed their eyes.</p>
<p>“Mścisław. Mścisław. Mścisław.”</p>
<p>They heard the first candle get lit.</p>
<p>“Mścisław. Mścisław. Mścisław.”</p>
<p>The window curtains rustled.</p>
<p>“Mścisław. Mścisław. Mścisław.”</p>
<p>The door creaked open.</p>
<p>“Mścisław. Mścisław. Mścisł-”</p>
<p>They were Mścisław. They didn’t recognize their own body. They didn’t know how they were alive.</p>
<p>“Did it work?” Akio said. “Is that why you stopped chanting?”</p>
<p>Their eyes widened and they looked up at their husband. “Akio.”</p>
<p>They rose and embraced him. Akio squeezed them tight. They missed him so much.</p>
<p>They held there a few moments before speaking. “My family is being shitty about me, about us, aren’t they?”</p>
<p>Akio nodded. “They barred me from attending your funeral, and that took place after a few months of legal battles over who got to hold it.”</p>
<p>Mścisław winced. “I’m so sorry, love.”</p>
<p>They kissed Akio on his lips. They held there for several moments savoring the feeling.</p>
<p>“It’s been months since I died,” they said. “I’m curious, why today?”</p>
<p>Akio grinned. “Don’t you know? Today’s February 14th. Our anniversary.”</p>
<p>They laughed and kissed Akio again. “You were always better about remembering it than I was.”</p>
<p>“I know it isn’t much,” he said, “but I got take out from dad’s restaurant. I wanted to be able to share it with you.”</p>
<p>“I’m the luckiest man in the world,” they said. “Every other man must wish they had such a sweet husband.”</p>
<p>“I’m only so sweet because I have such a wonderful husband to be sweet to.”</p>
<hr>
<p>Take out boxes lay discarded on Akio’s desk, long since gone cold. Mścisław leaned against it, facing his husband, their mouth fixed in a smile, but Akio’s gaze was fixed on the ground.</p>
<p>“What’s wrong, love?”</p>
<p>“Tonight has been wonderful.” Akio looked up with tears in his eyes. “I’ve missed you desperately.”</p>
<p>Mścisław nodded and placed their hand on his chest. “I’ll always be here with you. Even if I can’t talk to you directly, I will live on in you.”</p>
<p>He pulled them in for a hug and they could hear him sobbing. They gave his body a squeeze.</p>
<p>They said, “I have one last request for my husband.”</p>
<p>“What...” Akio’s voice is hoarse. He pulls away from the hug. “What is the request?”</p>
<p>“Keep on living. You will love me forever, but I don’t want you to dwell on me, for my memory to haunt you.” They bit back tears. “I want you to be happy even when I’m not able to support you.”</p>
<p>He nodded slowly. “I can do that.”</p>
<p>“Good bye, my love.”</p>
<p>They kissed Akio one last time and he returned the kiss.</p>
<p>He pulled away. “I will always remember you.”</p>
<p>Once again, they were only Star.</p>
<hr>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/ghost-crimes/">Read more Ghost Crimes.</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Ellesmere Eddas</title>
        <author>
            <name>Zara RW Storm</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/ellesmere-eddas/"/>
        <id>https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/ellesmere-eddas/</id>
            <category term="Eddas"/>

        <updated>2021-09-06T21:22:17-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    The following are poems about the divine Ellesmere written in the style of the Poetic Edda, that is using fornyrðislag verse. As such, they are each called "Edda"s. These are liable to later editing, more poems being added at a later time, and, perhaps, titles&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>The following are poems about the divine Ellesmere written in the style of the Poetic Edda, that is using fornyrðislag verse. As such, they are each called "Edda"s. These are liable to later editing, more poems being added at a later time, and, perhaps, titles added at some point. For now, they're being shared as is.</p>
<p>Below the Eddas is a description of various religious practices around Ellesmere with some theological ideas mixed in. Neither the religious practices nor the theological ideas are required. You shouldn’t feel an obligation to do or believe as is stated in here. Instead, they’re a guide for anyone who gets the inspiration to honor and worship Ellesmere.</p>
<p>Don't read these if you're not interested in learning about the described religious ideas and theology. This isn't something that's meant to be imposed on anyone, nor is there any expectation of adopting the religious beliefs endorsed by the poetry. These are means to share a particular religious perspective, not evangelical tools intent on conversion</p>
<p>In addition, Eddas 3 and 5 include sexual themes and Edda 3 includes allusions to violence. Feel free to skip it if such things bother you.</p>
<h4 class="align-center">The Eddas</h4>
<p><strong><br>Edda 1:</strong></p>
<p class="align-center">Long ago there   -  were two great gods.<br>The Leviathan   -   Vastness of the World.<br>The Wanderer   -   Roamer of the World.</p>
<p class="align-center">Encounter each other   -   to discover love.<br>Mix together   -   to merge as one.<br>Magnetic pull   -   to form two poles.</p>
<p class="align-center">Together become   -   great Ellesmere.<br>Named for the island   -   of magnetic North.<br>The World’s gift to   -   the wanderers.<br>Means by which   -   we can orient.</p>
<p class="align-center">Our god divine   -   oh great Ellesmere.<br>The love of two,   -   loving many.</p>
<p class="align-center"> </p>
<p><strong>Edda 2:</strong></p>
<p class="align-center">When Ellesmere   -   first enjoined.<br>Vulnerability   -   left ver distressed.</p>
<p class="align-center">Refuge was sought;   -   refuge was found.<br>In a fairy city   -   sie was welcomed.<br>A city of refuge,   -   for rest and safety.</p>
<p class="align-center">A Palace set into   -   an eternal rock.<br>Immense creation   -   of aged root.</p>
<p class="align-center">The city protected   -   the singular couple.<br>Fae gave it love   -   and love it returned.<br>Bound the city   -   to divine Ellesmere.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Edda 3:</strong></p>
<p class="align-center">Before history began,   -   the Wanderer; a hunting Beast.<br>Stalking ancient forests,   -   a Beast of charting journeys.<br>Brush and great tree   -   torn through forming paths.</p>
<p class="align-center">An ancient fairy flees   -   its unerring direction.<br>Beast of food wanting and lust,   -   prey of terror and desire.<br>Getting chase desired,   -   flight is sought for.</p>
<p class="align-center">The ritual of power,   -   the ritual of desire.<br>The prey always captured,   -   and always consumed.<br>Back again for another   -   hunt beneath gnarled wood.</p>
<p class="align-center">In the ritual of the hunt,   -   the beginning of roads forged.<br>A gift to humanity,   -   ways to wander forth; to grow and prosper.</p>
<p class="align-center">The fairy and the god,   -   once companions of gory lust.<br>Separated over time,   -   reunited in distant future.<br>A city giving love,   -   the fairy’s soul in its founding.<br>A fairy child among humanity,   -   with stolen power; the fairy’s soul.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Edda 4:</strong></p>
<p class="align-center">The serpent of the world,   -   great parent of the land.<br>The divine Leviathan   -   vastness in embodiment.<br>From hir springs fairies,   -   creatures of the rolling hills.</p>
<p class="align-center">Driven from the land,   -   hidden from the world’s vastness.<br>Dislocated from this god,   -   no longer in zir embrace.</p>
<p class="align-center">Petty squabbles;   -   petty kingdoms.<br>In absence of divinity,   -   in hiding underground.<br>Fairy kingdoms,   -   fairy queens.</p>
<p class="align-center">A plot of stolen power,   -   against the queen of winter.<br>A fairy child among humanity   -   broken time; reaching back.<br>Stealing from the past,   -   taking royal power.</p>
<p class="align-center">With power stolen,   -   a city forged.<br>Reunited with their god,   -   the vastness given love.<br>Worship once given,   -   worship now returned.<br>Division ended,   -   creatures with their divine.<br>Joyous reunion with their divine,  -    fairies lovingly embraced.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Edda 5:</strong></p>
<p class="align-center">Oh, divine Elesmere,   -   how you are love entire.<br>Oh, singular couple,   -   you are love encarnate.<br>The love of the Wanderer;   -   the love of the Leviathan.<br>Embodied twicefold,   -   love of both in one.</p>
<p class="align-center">For you love yourself,   -   you romance alone.<br>Here you play a game,   -   the body against the other.<br>You kiss and you fuck,   -   only yourself fooling around.<br>How you love and dance   -   in need of no other to love.</p>
<p class="align-center">Oh, to behold your beauty   -   it is the beauty of love.<br>To watch as you dance   -   your own dance partner.<br>As you love in yourself,   -   you love all who wander the world.</p>
<p class="align-center">To love you back,   -   for all who behold your embrace must weep.<br>A love who loves;   -   embodiment of loving itself.<br>In love, the pious must be   -   with loving so pure.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Edda 6:</strong></p>
<p class="align-center">Two gods becoming one   -   in glorious unity.<br>Even so, you must separate   -   into the lovers who compose you.<br>Separation as sweet   -   as the singularity you always become again.</p>
<p class="align-center">The Wanderer on hir paths,   -   you cannot simply be tied to one.<br>The Leviathan in zer totality,   -   you contain too much to only be one.</p>
<p class="align-center">Your separation so temporary,   -   yet important to the love entire.<br>The one must become two again   -   so you can become one again.<br>Separate you love   -   together you are love.<br>A beauty as both,   -   you beatify the loving.</p>
<p class="align-center">Paths that cross the land,   -   you love even separate.<br>Pious to each other,   -   worship of each other.</p>
<p class="align-center">Your love consecrates   -   the length of the globe.<br>Your love consecrates   -   getting lost on your journeys.</p>
<p class="align-center">Together again you always are   -   as love you have given form.</p>
<p><strong>Edda 7:</strong></p>
<p align="center">The Wanderer and the Leviathan;   -   Ellesmere, the well-spring of life.<br>Divine will and providence   -   provide its growth and evolution.<br>A structure and web of life;   -   the wide body of the Leviathan.<br>Growth, change, and development;   -   the great paths of the Wanderer.</p>
<p align="center">The body of the Leviathan   -   is vibrant life in totality.<br>From the microbe to the megafaun’,   -   faer body encompasses it all.<br>The firmament of life,   -   the whole of her large body.</p>
<p align="center">Belonging to the Wanderer   -   language lies deep within us all.<br>Our body’s plan and structure   -   speaks through our DNA.<br>Following paths to new places,   -   it mutates and transforms.</p>
<p align="center">The Wanderer provides   -   the Leviathan with change.<br>Hir pliant body transformed   -   by per lovers supple touch.<br>Their tryst that’s not yet here,   -   maintains their retrocause love</p>
<p align="center">Finally united as Ellesmere,   -   the fullness of their love actualized.<br>Together at last as one,   -   the singular couple is life.<br>The web of life as totality   -   and the language of transformation.<br>Together at last as one,   -   the singular couple is life.</p>
<p class="align-left" align="center"> </p>
<h4 class="align-center">Religious Practice</h4>
<p><br>Ellesmere, the Wanderer, and the Leviathan take any pronouns. Cycling through different pronouns or using different pronouns as the circumstances allow (such as choosing pronouns based on how it effects the alliterative verse) are encouraged.</p>
<p><strong>Festival</strong></p>
<p>Ellesmere formed from the Wanderer and the Leviathan on September 7th 2020. As such, September 7th is a festival in hir honor. It’s a day on which you should feel encouraged to express your love of all sorts, not just romantic, more boldly, but also a day to have a big party and share food and company with those you care about and love. Specific practices associated with such a festival aren’t set in stone and feel free to experiment as you may. More suggestions may be added here as this holiday is passed more frequently.</p>
<p><strong>Fusion</strong></p>
<p>Ellesmere exists as a fusion between two gods in love, but the merger of identity inherent to Ellesmere isn’t something held exclusively by the gods. The gods are, in many ways, greater beings, but there is no inherent separation. Fusion by the non-deific is just as possible as the formation of Ellesmere. An element of zir worship is forming these sorts of fusions yourself.</p>
<p>Importantly, you shouldn’t force a fusion like this, nor should you enter a relationship with someone for the purpose of fusing with them, nor is a romantic relationship specifically required. Fusion is a more organic process. It is the product of intense love, but not all love is romantic. Fusion is not for everyone and, while it’s a sort of worship, it’s not a sort of worship that’s required of anyone.</p>
<p>Healthy fusion is formed through an additive process where you take on characteristics of each other until you’ve achieved a shared state which allows for a singular coherent identity. It requires you to be willing to share everything with someone, to accept your differences with someone and to take on elements of those differences, and to trust someone totally. There is no singular process for doing fusion. It is a process unique to each fusion.</p>
<p><strong>Gnosis</strong></p>
<p>An element of Ellesmere worship is entering a gnosis state. A gnosis state is a state of altered consciousness which allows for the access to hidden knowledge, strange power, or ecstatic visions. It can be achieved with the aid of drugs or through methods of intense self-stimulation, but a method exalted to Ellesmere for entering such a state is through the intensity of sexual union. With enough mutual stimulation, you can enter into such a gnosis state together. This should be done with someone you trust. It’s an intense experience and shouldn’t be treated lightly.</p>
<p><strong>Amulet</strong></p>
<p>A small amulet you can make for Ellesmere is a small magnet without visually differentiated poles kept inside a small green bag of some sort. Example pictures included.</p>
<div class="gallery-wrapper gallery-wrapper--full"><div class="gallery"  data-is-empty="false" data-columns="4">
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140243835.jpg" data-size="x"><img loading="lazy" src="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140243835-thumbnail.jpg" alt="A stack of metal bars (magnets) with plastic dividers stuck together." width="720" height="540"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140248687.jpg" data-size="x"><img loading="lazy" src="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140248687-thumbnail.jpg" alt="A stack of .mall green bags with pull strings." width="720" height="960"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140302970.jpg" data-size="x"><img loading="lazy" src="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140302970-thumbnail.jpg" alt="A hand holding a small metal bar (a magnet)." width="720" height="960"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140316693.jpg" data-size="x"><img loading="lazy" src="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140316693-thumbnail.jpg" alt="A small metal bar (a magnet) sitting on a small green bag with pull strings." width="720" height="960"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140422970.jpg" data-size="x"><img loading="lazy" src="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140422970-thumbnail.jpg" alt="Six small metal bars (magnets) sitting on six small green bags with pullstrings." width="720" height="540"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140450555.jpg" data-size="x"><img loading="lazy" src="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140450555-thumbnail.jpg" alt="A small green bag with pull strings which is held open and a small metal bar (a magnet) being dropped in." width="720" height="960"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140502070.jpg" data-size="x"><img loading="lazy" src="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140502070-thumbnail.jpg" alt="A small green bag with pull strings pulled closed." width="720" height="960"></a></figure>
<figure class="gallery__item"><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140558424.jpg" data-size="x"><img loading="lazy" src="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/media/posts/8/gallery/IMG_20210203_140558424-thumbnail.jpg" alt="Several small green bags with pullstrings stuck together with one being held by the pullstrings and the others sticking to the first." width="720" height="540"></a></figure>
</div></div>
<p><strong>Shrines</strong></p>
<p>Small shrines to Ellesmere, to the Wanderer, and to the Leviathan, as well as to any other god you wish to honor, are a good form of veneration you can engage in. They’re useful for leaving offerings and engaging in prayer at. When one is able to be constructed, pictures will be added here.</p>
<p><strong>Approach to the World</strong></p>
<p>Finally, Ellesmere is a god of love, all love, and it’s important to allow that love to guide you and to build a world shaped by that love. Love of family, love of friends, love of romantic partners, love of strangers, love of yourself, etc. They are all important and fighting for a world based on them is the pious thing to do. Fighting oppression wherever its found, fighting for liberation wherever it’s needed. Not out of some high moral virtue, but because of your own love.</p>
<p>The Wanderer and the Leviathan also bring their own concerns to the table.</p>
<p>Life on the Leviathan is threatened by mass extinction, global warming, and various other such ecocidal phenomenon. This harms humans of all stripes, but it also destroys non-human ecosystems and devastates species around the Leviathan, all of which are important. It’s important that we fight to preserve life upon hir and against all the systems of power that serve to perpetuate such ecocide.</p>
<p>The path of the Wanderer is always long and varied and borders between nations serve to prevent natural movement around the Leviathan. Some wish to seek a better life in other places, a place different from their own, or refuge from instability, natural disaster, persecution, and war. It is incumbent on us to allow them to move freely rather than restricting them and fight for a world without borders.</p>
<p>The demands of love are not to be silent nor to avoid action when injustice rears its head, but to fight for it to end by whatever means necessary.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>A Certain Magic To Love</title>
        <author>
            <name>Zara RW Storm</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/a-certain-magic-to-love/"/>
        <id>https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/a-certain-magic-to-love/</id>
            <category term="Commissions"/>

        <updated>2021-09-06T21:22:17-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    An art trade with @TheR3dPainter. An arrow flew past Alok’s face and he winced. A thunk behind him and another arrow notched in front of him. He leapt to the side and rolled coming up to a crouch, an arrow flying wide. Ahead of him&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>An art trade with <a href="https://twitter.com/TheR3dPainter">@TheR3dPainter</a>.</p>
<p>An arrow flew past Alok’s face and he winced. A thunk behind him and another arrow notched in front of him. He leapt to the side and rolled coming up to a crouch, an arrow flying wide. Ahead of him one of the bandits fought Jespar with a sword, a wall between Alok and the archer. He didn’t have a good line of fire on the archer, not with Jespar in the way. Something needed to change.</p>
<p>He kept his distance and circled the fight to keep the archer in as much danger of hitting an ally as he was in. He was relying on Jespar to give him the opening he needed.</p>
<p>Jespar lunged forward. The bandit with a sword stepped to the side and moved in for Jespar. Alok realized the mistake he had made as he did as well. Jespar continued his forward momentum and shoved the bandit with his shoulder, knocking him off balance, then took several steps backward.</p>
<p>Jespar yelled, “Alok, now.”</p>
<p>Alok extended his hands forward and a bolt of lightning arced across the gap to the bandit. He gasped and fell. But the lightning didn’t stop. Alok focused on it to bring it to an end, but the magic kept flowing from him. The lightning leader searched for a new target. A bush sparked and a rabbit yelped, but neither maintained the bolt. Then it met with Jespar’s right arm who dropped one of his swords.</p>
<p>Jespar screamed in pain. Alok pulled on his hand, but it didn’t budge for a moment, and then the connection was broken. Smoke rose from Jespar’s arm. The archer stared at what happened, then turned and fled.</p>
<p>Alok rushed forward and knelt beside Jespar.</p>
<p>He reached out his hand. “Are you ok?”</p>
<p>Jespar flinched away and got up. “I’ll make camp.”</p>
<p>Jespar stalked off and Alok stared at his hands. He hadn’t meant to... Tears flowed unbidden. He sat there on the ground for several minutes before he could compose himself. He went to join Jespar at camp.</p>
<hr>
<p>A fire was lit in the camp by the time nightfall set. Jespar sat on a log, stoking the fire with a stick. He was using his left arm, not using his right arm. Alok approached the fire and sat by it, a short distance from Jespar.</p>
<p>“Do you...” Alok trailed off for a moment before continuing, “Do you want some help with your arm?”</p>
<p>Jespar stared at the fire in silence for several moments. “Yeah. That would be nice.”</p>
<p>Alok moved closer and examined the wound. The lightning had cauterized the hole it had dug into Jespar’s arm, but the blackness covering it was soot, not necrosis. It wasn’t good, but it would heal. He reached for Jespar’s sleeve, then stopped.</p>
<p>“May I?”</p>
<p>Jespar nodded and Alok pulled up the sleeve, careful not to touch the wound. He set some ointment and bandages out on the log.</p>
<p>“This is going to hurt a little.”<br>Jespar grimaced and his body tensed up. Carefully, Alok dabbed ointment on the wound. Jespar winced with each dab, but didn’t make any sounds. Alok rubbed more ointment onto the bandage itself then began wrapping it around his arm.</p>
<p>He paused the wrapping a second. “I’m sorry.” He continued wrapping. “I still don’t have full control over my magic, yet. But I would never want to hurt you.”</p>
<p>Jespar poked at the fire for a few moments. “Thank you. I don’t blame you for it. I guessed that’s what was the issue. It just hurts.”</p>
<p>Alok cut the bandage and tucked the end under the rest.</p>
<p>“I hope the ointment is helping with the pain.”</p>
<p>Jespar nodded slowly. “It is.”</p>
<p>Alok smiled. “I’m glad. I hate to see you in pain like this.”</p>
<p>He hesitated a moment and then kissed the outside of the bandage.</p>
<p>“A kiss to make it feel better.”</p>
<p>A slight blush entered Jespar’s face and he looked away.</p>
<p>“It’s feeling better already,” He said. “I can feel the magic working.”</p>
<p>Alok laughed and gently took Jespar’s hand is his own.</p>
<p>“There is a certain magic to that sort of thing.”</p>
<p>Jespar looked back at him. “What sort of thing?”</p>
<p>“To love, of course.” Alok grinned at Jespar. “There are few magics more powerful.”</p>
<p>They both stayed in place for a few moments, then Jespar kissed Alok on his forehead.</p>
<p>“Thank you.” Jespar hesitated for a moment. “I love you too.”</p>
<p>Alok’s face flushed and he buried it against Jespar’s sleeve, bundled up against his shoulder. It was the first time he’d said that.</p>
<p>They sat there hand in hand with the fire for the rest of the night and fell asleep against each other, happy.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>First Contact</title>
        <author>
            <name>Zara RW Storm</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/first-contact/"/>
        <id>https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/first-contact/</id>
            <category term="Commissions"/>

        <updated>2021-09-06T21:22:17-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Written for @Mocharaid on Twitter. The stars twinkled far above the Earth. Since antiquity, humans stared up at them wondering if they stared back. Modern science assured them that the stars do not stare back. They sit light years away, burning balls of gas. Little&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Written for <a href="https://twitter.com/Mocharaid">@Mocharaid</a> on Twitter.</p>
<p>The stars twinkled far above the Earth. Since antiquity, humans stared up at them wondering if they stared back. Modern science assured them that the stars do not stare back. They sit light years away, burning balls of gas. Little did they know that they did watch. They watched as society developed from simple kings to complex slave societies, from feudal kingdoms to capitalist empires.</p>
<p>The Ek’en’ had long moved beyond what they saw on the planet. Wars between nations, genocides constructing those nations justifying billions exploited for profit by a ruling class. From their perch among the stars, they saw in the Earth their past of brutality, exploitation, and domination.</p>
<p>But Earth wasn’t content to stagnation. The planet rose up against their masters and tore apart their chains. Capitalism poisoned the water, polluted the air, and destroyed the forests. But the mass of workers tore it apart piece by piece. A new society, no longer organized around hierarchy and domination, but through free association of producers.</p>
<p>In the sky of this new world a shooting star fell. A round metal ball up close, with four wire legs trailing behind. This spaceship, the Ente’resh, housed three three long legged birds with impressive crests. Ned’era checked the engines, zar crest bright green. Akel’esh manned the controls, err crest golden. Ek’ibe’ paced furtively, its crest grey.</p>
<p>Akel’esh guided the ship through the atmosphere at a breakneck speed. Esh pulled back on a bar on the control panel with err clawed foot and the descent began to slow. Below, a city approached. Skyscrapers covered in plants, vines hanging down their sides, flowers blooming against them. Life overflowed.</p>
<p>On the ground, humans sauntered about talking with each other as they move around. The ship slowed as it approached the city, casting a shadow over the crowd. They stalled above the crowd and hovered there for a moment as the crowd parted to let them touch down.</p>
<p>Ek’ibe’ led the three of them out of the ship with a flutter of its wings.</p>
<p>“Greetings, humans.” It bowed respectfully. “I am Ek’ibe’ of the Ek’en’. These are my comrades Akel’esh and Ned’era. We have watched your people for a long time and I am proud to be able to finally meet you.”</p>
<p>The crowd stared. Whispers passed through the crowd. Finally, one human stepped forth.</p>
<p>“It is nice to meet you, Ek-uh-ibe-uh,” the human said, mangling the pronunciation of its name. “I am Sam. You can refer to me with xe/xem pronouns. It is nice to meet you.”</p>
<p>Xe bowed, mimicking the bow it had given the crowd, then extended a hand toward it. Ek’ibe’ took xyr hand and shook it. First contact between two free peoples.</p>
<hr>
<p>See more about commissions <a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/commissions/">here</a>.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Commissions</title>
        <author>
            <name>Zara RW Storm</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/commissions/"/>
        <id>https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/commissions/</id>
            <category term="Commissions"/>

        <updated>2021-09-06T21:22:17-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    If you want a story written, DM me @deathpigeon on Twitter or deathpigeon@gmail.com via email. Commissions cost $5 per 100 words (rounded up). The longer the story the longer it will take me, I have no guarantee on the timescale for writing. I'm not comfortable&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>If you want a story written, DM me <a href="https://twitter.com/deathpigeon">@deathpigeon</a> on Twitter or <a href="mailto:deathpigeon@gmail.com">deathpigeon@gmail.com</a> via email.</p>
<p>Commissions cost $5 per 100 words (rounded up). The longer the story the longer it will take me, I have no guarantee on the timescale for writing. I'm not comfortable writing porn and I reserve the right to refuse any commission for any reason.</p>
<p>Commissions I've written:</p>
<p><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/first-contact/">First Contact</a> for <a href="https://twitter.com/Mocharaid">@Mocharaid</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/a-certain-magic-to-love/">A Certain Magic To Love</a> an art trade with <a href="https://twitter.com/TheR3dPainter">@TheR3dPainter</a>.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Taken To The Grave (Ghost Crimes #2)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Zara RW Storm</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/taken-to-the-grave-ghost-crimes-2/"/>
        <id>https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/taken-to-the-grave-ghost-crimes-2/</id>
            <category term="Ghost Crimes"/>

        <updated>2021-09-06T21:22:17-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Content Warning: Alcohol and Cigarette Use, Mild Police Violence, Police Intimidation, Police Interrogation, Parental Abuse, Ableism, Spirit Possession “Surely you can’t be suggesting that you can talk your way out of every spiritual situation,” Aaron said, his voice level. “Some spirits are hostile and need&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p class="align-center">Content Warning: Alcohol and Cigarette Use, Mild Police Violence, Police Intimidation, Police Interrogation, Parental Abuse, Ableism, Spirit Possession</p>
<hr>
<p>“Surely you can’t be suggesting that you can talk your way out of every spiritual situation,” Aaron said, his voice level. “Some spirits are hostile and need to be treated as such.”</p>
<p>Star sat at a wood slab table next to Aaron at Raised Spirits surrounded by the bar’s familiar hum of quiet conversation, not so loud as to overwhelm. Aaron was the spitting image of a Irish catholic priest: ginger hair, a wide grin, and a roman collar beneath his black shirt.</p>
<p>Star shook their head. “That’s not the point. It’s not about if the spirit will listen or is hostile. Sometimes a confrontation is inevitable, but, if you enter the situation with the assumption of that inevitability, then you’re ensuring its outcome.”</p>
<p>Star took a gulp of their drink. It went down smooth, tasting of raspberries. They hadn’t picked it themself, but had relied on Silvia, the bartender and their long time friend, to choose it for them.</p>
<p>“Star. Child. I am called in to situations where the spirit is already hostile. It isn’t an assumption that confrontation is inevitable. It is the situation I specialize in.”</p>
<p>“I understand, Father.” Star bowed their head momentarily. “But that a spirit is already hostile doesn’t mean they can’t be talked down. Your assumption is that the state the spirit is in upon your arrival is inherent to that spirit. Spirits aren’t any different from you or me. If you...”</p>
<p>Star stopped. The air grew cold. Not by much, but enough that Star was able to notice the change. The wind moved through the space as if by a mind of its own.</p>
<p>They thought, <i>No, not as if...</i></p>
<p>“Excuse me? Star?” Aaron’s voice broke through. “If I... what?”</p>
<p>Star leaned in to Aaron and whispered, “Something is here.”</p>
<p>The hairs on the back of their neck stood on end. A hand rested on their shoulder.</p>
<p>“I’m sorry for the intrusion,” said a voice in their ear, “but I really must speak to the Father.”</p>
<p>They were Henri.</p>
<p>“Hello, Father Aaron.” Their head bowed deep for several seconds. “I would like to plead for your help in a matter I would only trust you in.”</p>
<p>Aaron stared at them. He downed the rest of his drink.</p>
<p>“How may I help you, child?”</p>
<p>“My grave has been robbed,” Henri said, “A priceless family heirloom has been taken. I fear that one of my children may be the culprit. I would like it back, but I do not want to see my family go to jail. Will you help me, Father? I do not know who else I can turn to.”</p>
<p>“Of course, child.” Aaron said, “I will do what I can to help you.”</p>
<p>They were Star, again. Henri hadn’t left. But he had stepped back.</p>
<p>Star said, “And I can help you too, Henri.”</p>
<p>“Thank you, Father.” Henri said, “Thank you, shaman. We should depart from this place and visit the scene of the crime.”</p>
<p>The three of them got in Aaron’s car to go to the graveyard. The car ride was silent. It was dark outside and the only light was from cars around them. The light hurt their eyes. Sirens split the quiet. They were approaching the graveyard. Lights flashed red and blue. Aaron parked and the three of them exited the car.</p>
<p>Star grimaced. “Well, looks like we’re too late to beat the cops.”</p>
<p>“We can surely ask them what’s going on, child.”</p>
<p>Star rolled their eyes. Aaron shrugged and walked toward the cops alone. His mouth moved to speak, but he was too far for them to hear.</p>
<p>“Why don’t you scram?” A voice behind Star said, “This is a crime scene. We don’t need any of your crack pottery here.”</p>
<p>Star turned and blanched. The figure in front of them held herself like a hardboiled detective on the hunt. Her glower, her scowl, her tense shoulders, and her hand on her gun, all directed at them.</p>
<p>“Hi, Lisa,” they said. “It’s always so nice to see you.”</p>
<p>Lisa glared. “That’s Detective Lisa.”</p>
<p>“Well, Lisa, my ride is over there,” Star waved toward Aaron, “talking to the cops while you’re here harassing an innocent bystander.”</p>
<p>“You’re loitering by a crime scene.” Lisa grimaced. “And you’re a fraud. Sounds like you’re planning on swindling someone.”</p>
<p>Star said, “That’s hardly a fair-”</p>
<p>Lisa cut in. “Unless you’re here to help the thief. This sort of occult mumbo jumbo is your stock and trade.”</p>
<p>Lisa took a step toward them. They took several steps back.</p>
<p>Star rose their voice and said, “It’s not a great idea for a cop to harass someone with so many witnesses around. Especially not with a priest around.”</p>
<p>The cops and Aaron across the street turned to see what was going on. Aaron hurried across the street.</p>
<p>“Detective,” Aaron said, “What seems to be the problem here?”</p>
<p>Lisa waved her hand at Star. “We have a known charlatan here loitering by the crime scene. For all I know, they’re looking to help the thief.”</p>
<p>“Lisa, please,” Star said, “These accusations aren’t helping anything. Are you detaining me or am I free to go?”</p>
<p>Lisa turned back to Star and glared. “You aren’t free to go. In fact, you’re going to come with me to the precinct to answer a few questions. Face this car and put your hands against it where I can see them.”</p>
<p>They complied. Aaron stared. Lisa pulled their hands behind their back and cuffed them.</p>
<p>“Don’t worry, Star.” Aaron said, “I’ll get a lawyer to the station as soon as I can.”</p>
<p>Star smiled. “Thank you, friend.”</p>
<hr>
<p>Star’s hands were cuffed behind their back. The cuffs chaffed on their wrists, but didn’t do real damage. The back seat of the police car was hard plastic. There was no room for them to fit their hands. A beat cop drove them to the station.</p>
<p>They sat in the station waiting for their name to be called. Time crawled. Their name was called. Booking was mostly paperwork done by the cops.</p>
<p>They were led to small table in a small office store room, uncuffed, and left alone. Behind the shut door, a fan hummed, leaving the room running hot. The chair hurt their back, hard as concrete.</p>
<p>The door opened and a cop entered with a bottle of water. He towered over Star, but his posture was relaxed and his skin as dark as their own.</p>
<p>“Are you thirsty?” The cop said holding the bottle out.</p>
<p>Star nodded.</p>
<p>The cop smiled and sat next to Star. “Well, son...”</p>
<p>Star winced at that.</p>
<p>“I need to ask you some questions,” The cop continued. “You were there at the scene of the crime after all. Then I can give you some water.”</p>
<p>Star grimaced. “I’d like to speak to a lawyer.”</p>
<p>“A lawyer is coming. I’d just like to get you out of here as soon as possible, but I need you to answer my questions, first.”</p>
<p>Star stared down at the ground. They said nothing. Thirst overwhelmed their thoughts.</p>
<p><i>Maybe I should just talk. Get the water.</i> They thought. But that was a silly idea. Water and comfort weren’t worth jail time. And the cops wouldn’t accept that the ghost of the corpse in the looted grave asked for their help.</p>
<p>“I just want to know,” the cop said, “what brought you to that graveyard. I’m sure you had a very good reason for it.”</p>
<p>Star’s gaze wandered to the water in the cop’s hand. Their arm moved slightly toward it, but they stopped it.</p>
<p>The cop continued. “I know, I know. You give your clients confidentiality. I wouldn’t disrespect your professional pride by asking you to tell me anything private. But this is all off the record. Just a friendly chat. And you’d help me out a lot by just telling me what you can tell.”</p>
<p>Star’s voice cracked as they spoke, “Can I please have some water?”</p>
<p>The cop smiled. “I just need some information. I can give you some water, but I need something from you, first.”</p>
<p>Star shook their head. “It’s just very hot in this room. I can barely talk.”</p>
<p>“Ah,” the cop said, “I understand. The thermostat in here is always broken. But I don’t need you to do much talking. I can just ask you some simple yes or no questions and you can nod or shake your head.”</p>
<p>Star stared at the water. They thought, <i>It’s not much to just nod...</i> The offer was tempting. And their will was weakening. That was probably the point of the water and the heat. Not the faulty thermostat. The degradation of will.</p>
<p>The cop said, “Were you there on behalf of a client?”</p>
<p>Star stayed still.</p>
<p>“Were you called by the spirits of that place?”</p>
<p>Star trembled a bit from the thirst. They didn’t shake their head or nod.</p>
<p>“Ah, I understand,” The cop smiled. “You don’t think that I believe in spirits. It’s true that Detective Lisa is a bit of a hardass about that. But I have no reason to not believe you. My aunt could hear the spirits around her. She’d talk about it every Thanksgiving.”</p>
<p>Star couldn’t hold back coughing. The thirst hurt.</p>
<p>“I’m sure that whatever secrets the spirits have are yours alone, and I wouldn’t want to infringe upon that. I just would like to know-”</p>
<p>The door to this room opened. In stepped a tall man in a professional suit.</p>
<p>The newcomer said, “I’m sorry to interrupt you, officer, but my client doesn’t need to answer any of your questions.”</p>
<p>The cop shrugged. “It was worth a try.”</p>
<p>The newcomer turned to Star. “Hey, are you doing ok?”</p>
<p>Star shook their head, not trusting themself to speak.</p>
<p>“May I,” the lawyer said, “take my client somewhere more comfortable? Or are they charged with a crime?”</p>
<p>The cop sighed. “You are free to go.”</p>
<p>The newcomer, a lawyer, helped Star up and they walked out of the interrogation room. The lawyer signed off on some paperwork. They stopped by a vending machine and the lawyer bought them a soda which they drank thirstily. Then they left the precinct.</p>
<p>Aaron was waiting outside.</p>
<p>He nodded at the lawyer. “Thank you, Andrew.”</p>
<p>“It’s not a problem, Father.” The lawyer, Andrew, smiled. “I’m familiar with the detective in question. She’s a menace.”</p>
<p>“And how are you doing, child?” Aaron turned to Star. “Were you well treated?”</p>
<p>Star sighed. “The cop tried to be friendly, but he kept a bottle of water as leverage to get me to answer his questions. It was hot in that room.”</p>
<p>Andrew cut in. “Did you tell them anything?”</p>
<p>Star shook their head.</p>
<p>“Good,” Andrew said, “Talking with cops like that is just a liability.”</p>
<p>He handed Star a business card.</p>
<p>“If you ever get harassed by that detective again, please call me. I’m sure that Father Aaron would be happy to cover the costs.”</p>
<p>Star took the card. “Thank you.”</p>
<p>Aaron and Andrew exchanged some words, then Andrew departed. Aaron offered to drive Star home. The drive happened in silence.</p>
<p>Star said good bye to Aaron at their apartment walked in and collapsed on their bed. They curled up into a ball and sobbed.</p>
<hr>
<p>Star woke up groggily.</p>
<p>“Are you ok?” Their friend Zee was sitting on their chest staring down at them.</p>
<p>In a crowd, they wouldn’t even notice Zee. Up close, they were able to study eir features. Eir eyes were a soft brown, pretty when studied. E scrunched up eir button nose and tightened eir thin lips into a slight frown.</p>
<p>They sighed. “Normal people don’t do this with eir friends.”</p>
<p>“Well, I’m not normal,” Zee said. “Plus, I was worried about you. You got arrested last night.”</p>
<p>“It was that detective who has it out for me,” Star said. “Aaron hired a lawyer and got me out. I’m fine.”</p>
<p>Zee frowned down at them.</p>
<p>“Can you get off my chest?” Star waved em off. “I’d like to make some breakfast.”</p>
<p>Zee slid off. “I made you some eggs and coffee.”</p>
<p>E offered a hand to help Star up and they took it.</p>
<p>There were sunny side up eggs with some toast and coffee waiting for them in the kitchen.</p>
<p>Star said, “I don’t have eggs in the apartment. Or coffee this good.”</p>
<p>Zee slid off. “I made you some eggs and coffee.”</p>
<p>E offered a hand to help Star up and they took it.</p>
<p>Standing, they could take in eir whole body. A simple white tank top adorned eir beige binder and exposed muscles which they wouldn't have noticed from afar. Eir frame was slim while eir skin was smooth and well-maintained. Star’s stomach grumbled and they dug into the eggs.</p>
<p>“Yeah, well, I bought you groceries.” Zee smiled and sat on the kitchen counter. “You had a rough night, and I figured you’d appreciate the help. I know what you like.”</p>
<p>Star raised an eyebrow. “Bought?”</p>
<p>Zee splayed eir hands. “I can’t guarantee the money I bought them with was legally procured, but the groceries were bought with cash.”</p>
<p>Star laughed. They nearly choked on their eggs.</p>
<p>Zee frowned. “What?”</p>
<p>“I’m just imagining,” Star said, “you walking around a store like a normal person buying groceries.”</p>
<p>Zee giggled. “It’s true. I don’t do that very often. But, for you, I made a special exception.”</p>
<p>Star finished their eggs in silence. They took a drink of the coffee. Dark, but with a bit of whiskey mixed in. Perfect for a shitty morning.</p>
<p>“Thank you,” Star said. “The food was delicious.”</p>
<p>Zee smiled. “It’s no problem.”</p>
<p>E patted the counter next to em. Star hopped up as well.</p>
<p>“So,” Zee said, “What got that detective to stick her nose in your business?”</p>
<p>Star grimaced. “Well, it’s more like I stuck my nose in her business. Not on purpose. My latest client is just... Related to one of her cases.”</p>
<p>Zee nodded. “The grave robbery.”</p>
<p>“Yes,” Star said. “It’s... I was having a disagreement with Aaron last night about the nature of our respective work. And we were interrupted by the ghost of the inhabitant of that grave. He asked for Aaron’s help, but I’m a necessary go between.”</p>
<p>Star took a long drink of coffee. “He thinks someone in his family did it. He’d prefer for a catholic priest to convince whoever did it to return what was stolen than for them to get arrested.”</p>
<p>Zee nodded. “I understand. Do you need any help?”</p>
<p>Star drank more of the coffee. They stared down at it as it swirled. “Look into the father. I can’t help him unless I know more about him.”</p>
<p>“Absolutely,” Zee said. “I’ll even do it pro bono.”</p>
<p>Star smiled. “Thank you, Zee. You’re a good friend.”</p>
<p>They sat there together on the counter. Star drank more of their coffee. Zee leaned against them, eir shoulder resting against their upper arm.</p>
<p>Someone whacked on the door, snapping their heads to it and then one another.</p>
<p>Zee ran to the back window. Star walked to the door, slowly. E gave them a salute before slipping out through the window. They opened the door.</p>
<p>“Good morning, Star.” Aaron smiled at them. “It’s nice to see you doing well. And are those eggs I smell?”</p>
<p>No one stood with Aaron visibly, but he wasn’t alone.</p>
<p>Star nodded. “Eggs for one, unfortunately.”</p>
<p>“Oh, it’s ok,” Aaron said. “I wouldn’t want to impose. How was your night?”</p>
<p>Star lowered their head. “It was rough. But this morning was better.”</p>
<p>Aaron raised his eyebrows. “You’re blushing. Someone was here this morning, then.”</p>
<p>Star’s hand went to their cheeks. They hadn’t realized they’d been blushing. They took a long drink of coffee.</p>
<p>“So,” They said, “do we have a plan for helping Henri? He came with you.”</p>
<p>Aaron nodded. “I set up a brunch with his daughter.”</p>
<p>“I did have breakfast,” Star said. “Should I really go to brunch, now?”</p>
<p>“Oh, of course, child.” Aaron smiled kindly. “You’re hungry far too often.”</p>
<p>Star quickly changed into fresh clothes. Nothing too fancy, but something serviceable. They chatted as the three of them walked down to Aaron’s car. They got in. Star held the door open long enough for Henri to enter with them.</p>
<p>They drove to a breakfast shop. Noise of overlapping conversation spilled over Star. They grimaced and took a deep breath before walking between the tables that littered the thin patio space outside. The smell of fresh coffee hit them as they entered and Aaron asked for the table with ‘Tatienne’.</p>
<p>An aroma of incense greeted when they got to the table. Tatienne stood stiffly. Her mouth was a thin line, frowning and a necklace rested against her chest. It showed a unicursal hexagon, a symbol associated with the occult religion Thelema.</p>
<p>Aaron extended his hand to her to shake. “Thank you for meeting us on such short notice.”</p>
<p>Tatienne accepted his hand. “It’s not a problem at all. Please, sit.”</p>
<p>She motioned for them to sit and they both did. She stared briefly at Star before returning to her seat.</p>
<p>“So, then,” Tatienne said, “what is it that a priest and a... Who are you, again?”</p>
<p>Star opened their mouth, but Aaron cut in.</p>
<p>“This is a colleague of mine,” he said. “They are consulting with me on a matter which requires their particular skill set.”</p>
<p>Tatienne raised an eyebrow. “And what is this matter that you are dealing with? You were quite vague on the phone.”</p>
<p>Aaron smiled. “An anonymous party requested that I look into the matter with your father’s grave.”</p>
<p>Tatienne’s eyes widened and her grip on her drink tightened.</p>
<p>“The man I spoke to,” Aaron continued, “is convinced that it was done by someone in a place of spiritual crisis. I am not a cop. I am a priest. It isn’t my job to seek retribution, but forgiveness for sin. So he asked that I intercede in the matter and convince whoever has stolen the item to return it before the police arrest them.”</p>
<p>Tatienne took a long deep breath and straightened her back. "So, what are they here for? I'm not sure what skills they might provide to your endeavor."</p>
<p>“I am here,” Star said, “to act as a point of contact for the party who asked for intercession and to act as a neutral party representing his interests. I have experience in matters like this and with clients like the one this case brings with it. Any action I take in this matter is to represent those who aren’t here to speak for themself, the client and any other relevant parties.”</p>
<p>Tatienne cocked her head. She nodded slowly. “In that case, I don’t know what help I could provide. I haven’t spoken to my father in years. My brother, Theo, is also in town. He might be able to help you more.”</p>
<p>Star said, “We haven’t even asked you anything, yet.”</p>
<p>“You don’t need to,” She said. “I don’t have anything to give you. I’ll speak to the staff here and pay for your brunch, but I can’t help and I’m not interested in wasting my time.”</p>
<p>She got up and left.</p>
<p>“Well,” Aaron said, “she was eager to end this conversation before it began.”</p>
<p>Star sighed and stared at their lap. “What a perfectly useless meeting. I’m not even hungry for brunch.”</p>
<p>“Nor am I,” Aaron said. “Perhaps we should reconvene somewhere more private so we can discuss this with everyone involved?”</p>
<p>They left the store. Outside, the wind picked up slightly. Star felt a slight chill. They were Henri.</p>
<p>Henri sighed. “Tatienne has always been stubborn.”</p>
<p>Aaron raised an eyebrow. “Perhaps. But that’s a conversation for in the car.”</p>
<p>In the car, Aaron said, “What happened between the two of you?”</p>
<p>“It’s nothing,” Henri said. “She got her stubbornness from me. And, when we are stubborn in divergent directions, that means there isn’t always a clear solution to the problem. It’s not relevant to any of this.”</p>
<p>Aaron frowned. “If you say so.”</p>
<p>“What of Theo?”</p>
<p>Aaron smiled. “Ah, Theo said that Tatienne might be like that on the phone. That’s why I scheduled her for brunch, and him for lunch in a few hours.”</p>
<p>“Ah.” Henri smiled. “That sounds like Theo.”</p>
<p>They were Star, again. Henri flowed into the back seat of the car.</p>
<p>They said, “So what do we <i>do</i> until then?”</p>
<p>“We could go to church,” Aaron said. “Perhaps God can give us some guidance.”</p>
<p>Star glared at Aaron for a moment, then sighed.</p>
<p>Aaron smiled. “Don’t worry, child. I was joking.”</p>
<hr>
<p>Soft light greeted them when they entered the building. Paintings hung haphazardly on the wall and cheap white tablecloths covered the flimsy tables.</p>
<p>Star waved a hand in front of their face to try to get rid of the reek of sizzling steaks. “A steakhouse?” Star whispered. “Really? That’s where we’re meeting him?”</p>
<p>Aaron shrugged. “I didn’t choose the accommodations. I’m sure they’ll have <i>something</i> you can eat.”</p>
<p>“It doesn’t even look like a particularly good steakhouse.”</p>
<p>“It’s a chain. But you should <i>see</i> the prices on this menu.”</p>
<p>Star said, “Gods. I don’t even want to know. It’s definitely too expensive for this place.”</p>
<p>“Ah!” A voice boomed behind them. “The priest and his assistant! So glad of you to join me!”</p>
<p>They turned. Behind them stood a tall man who reeked of cigars, bad cologne, and unearned superiority. He wore an expensive suit and a big grin on his face.</p>
<p>“It’s nice to meet you, Theo,” Aaron said. “We spoke on the phone.”</p>
<p>Theo adjusted his tie, flashing his gold watch. “Come, we can go to my regular table, here. Lunch is on me.”</p>
<p>They sat with him. The restaurant was empty. The restaurant had just opened. Aaron explained why they were here, just like with Tatienne. Theo had no questions about Star.</p>
<p>“You want to know about my father?” Theo said. “So you can catch the thief. A real Sherlock Holmes and Watson.” He pointed to Aaron then Star.</p>
<p>Star nodded. “We want to know about his relationship to you and any other family who are in town.”</p>
<p>“First,” He said, “let’s order food.”</p>
<p>Theo flagged down a waitress.</p>
<p>He leered at her. “I’d like my regular, hon.”</p>
<p>Star grimaced and stared at their lap. Aaron glared at him.</p>
<p>“What?” Theo said. “I can’t play the field?”</p>
<p>Aaron ordered a simple fish filet. Star ordered a salad and some asparagus and a raspberry cosmo.</p>
<p>Food came. Theo got a steak with shrimp and a bottle of red wine.</p>
<p>Theo took a bite. “So, my dad,” he said, chewing, “He was great <i>to me.</i> He stood by me through my whole MBA, even when I got that drunk driving charge.”</p>
<p>Theo swallowed. He cut another piece of his steak off and put it in his mouth.</p>
<p>“That said,” he continued, “he was pretty shit to Tristan. He was my brother. Real schizo sort. Y’know. Hallucinations. Paranoia. The whole shebang. Good kid, tho. Dad didn’t treat him right.”</p>
<p>Star grimaced and poked at their salad. They didn’t like how he spoke about Tristan.</p>
<p>Theo drunk some of his wine, then took another bite. “If I’d be honest, I was kinda shit to him, too. He doesn’t speak to me, still. Not since he ran away from home. But Tatienne was close to him. She took dad’s treatment of him personally, for some reason.”</p>
<p>Aaron said, “So you think this has to do with the theft?”</p>
<p>“Oh, yeah,” Theo said. “The theft. Forgot about that. No clue who could’ve done it. But you talked to Tatienne, however briefly. Thought I’d fill you in on why she can be a bitch about this sometimes.”</p>
<p>They asked him more questions, but he didn’t have anything else to offer. Theo paid for their food and the two of them left.</p>
<p>“Henri?” Star said in the car. “Your son kinda sucks.”</p>
<p>The air in the car was perfectly still. No response.</p>
<p>Aaron said, “Would you like to go home, Star?”</p>
<p>Star nodded. He drove them to their apartment. They said goodbye and watched as Aaron drove off.</p>
<p>They turned toward their apartment and began walking. Out of the shadows stepped Lisa, her hand resting on her holstered gun.</p>
<p>She said, “Finished with your a hard day’s work scamming people?”</p>
<p>“Hi, Lisa.” Star sighed. “You know me better than to think I’d just talk to you like this.”</p>
<p>“I do know you,” she said. “But just because you won’t talk doesn’t mean there’s no reason for me to chat with you when you get home from... Who was it you saw? Ah, yes, two citizens who’s father’s grave was just robbed.”</p>
<p>Star’s eyes widened.</p>
<p>“Ah, you didn’t think I’d have someone follow you?” Lisa grinned, “You are one of my top suspects in that theft. I’m not going to let you out of the sight of law enforcement.”</p>
<p>“Hey, buzz off.” From the direction of their apartment stood Silvia like a guardian angel. She held herself with righteous confidence and her light brown skin glowed from the light of the streetlamps behind them. Her low cut top gave a lot for Star to stare at, but they lingered on her well built and hot muscles.</p>
<p>She said, “Go harass someone else so I can check in on my friend you arrested last night.”</p>
<p>Lisa turned slowly. She glared at Silvia for a minute. She returned the glare.</p>
<p>“Fine.” She turned and stalked off. “But I’m watching you.</p>
<p>They both waited for her to leave.</p>
<p>Silvia moved toward them and her arms moved slightly up. She hesitated then they dropped to her side.</p>
<p>She said, “Are you ok?”</p>
<p>Star nodded. “Yeah. Aaron helped me out and I had a good breakfast with a friend.”</p>
<p>They opened their door and Silvia followed. They sat on their bed and Silvia stood above them.</p>
<p>She said, “What happened?”</p>
<p>“I swear that detective has it in for me ,” Star said. “I was outside one of her crime scenes for a client and she arrested me. They interrogated me. I told them nothing. A lawyer Aaron hired intervened.”</p>
<p>Silvia nodded slowly. “That bitch.”</p>
<p>Star laughed. “Yeah, no kidding.”</p>
<p>They walked into their apartment and Silvia followed close behind.</p>
<p>She smiled at them. “So what was the client who brought you to her crime scene?”</p>
<p>Star filled her in on the case.</p>
<p>“The daughter is key to this,” Silvia said. “The son is a dick, but she dodged your questions.”</p>
<p>Star nodded. “She also didn’t bring up Tristan. Theo said that she was the only one who still talked to him.”</p>
<p>“But what does that have to do with what was stolen?” Silvia said. “That’s what I don’t get. We know about his family trouble. He was a dick to his son and is estranged from his daughter as a result. And his other son grew up to be a dick as well. Not a great father, overall. But that’s not <i>motive</i>.”</p>
<p>“Ah, well.” Star grinned. “That’s where my secret weapon comes in. Zee was here this morning and I asked em to check into this. I’m hoping that e can fill in the blanks left by this thoroughly frustrating family. Not sure when e’ll have the information, but I’m hoping it’ll be tonight. For now, we just need to wait.”</p>
<p>Silvia nods. “After all you’ve been through yesterday and today, what say you to a good dinner?”</p>
<p>Star shifted their face away from her, their cheeks flushed. “Yeah. That sounds good. Zee bought me groceries. Plenty to make”</p>
<p>Silvia grinned. “You rest up. I’ll be right on it.”</p>
<p>They flopped back on their bed.</p>
<p><i>If I knew getting arrested would have Zee and Silvia treating me this way,</i> Star thought, <i>I'd've gotten arrested earlier.</i></p>
<p>Oh, both of them were nice on good days. They were their best friends. Some of their only friends. Without them, they'd just have John, Aaron, and Ezra. But John was never around these days with his job. Aaron was a priest, so not exactly the best company. And Ezra was just a whole thing and they didn't talk to it on a daily basis. Besides, the power behind its magic often made dealing with it difficult.</p>
<p>But today they had been pampered. Zee bought them groceries and made them breakfast. And Silvia was in their apartment making them dinner.</p>
<p>They rolled over and buried their face in their pillow at the thought. They were a mess. Getting flustered over friends making them food.</p>
<p>Silvia’s voice cut in from above them. “Hey, Star. Food is ready.”</p>
<p>Silvia stood above them with two bowls. Star took one of the chili filled bowls and dug in. It was spicy and warm, a flavor they were used to since they were a teenager.</p>
<p>“Thank you, Silvia.”</p>
<p>“It’s no problem,” She said. “You’re in a rough place, so I’m helping. It’s what friends do.”</p>
<p>She was sitting next to them. They hadn’t noticed her sit down. She reached out a hand and gripped theirs in her own. She gave it a little squeeze. They smiled.</p>
<p>The front door opened. Zee stepped in.</p>
<p>“Hi, Silvia.” Zee grinned at the two of them. “Hi, Star.”</p>
<p>Her hand separated from theirs. They both got up.</p>
<p>“Hey, Zee.” Star smiled back at em. “I was hoping you’d come by tonight. What’ve you got?”</p>
<p>“First things first,” Zee said. “I smell chili.”</p>
<p>Silvia made em a bowl and all three sat back down on the bed, Star in between the two.</p>
<p>“The city records office has such lax security,” Zee said. “I could’ve walked in the front door and gotten anything I wanted, even sealed files. It was almost comically easy.”</p>
<p>Silvia grinned at em. “And what did you find?”</p>
<p>“Well, first, court files.” Zee pulled some files from eir messenger bag. “These show that Henri tried to get his son locked up in an asylum at 17 years old. Absolutely disgusting. It didn’t work and it sounds like he ran away from home after that. Good for him.”</p>
<p>Star frowned. “Tristan, right?”</p>
<p>“Exactly.” Zee nodded. “Furthermore, he had been cut out of the will. And this is where things get interesting. The will before he got cut out included some sort of pendant or locket or amulet or whatever. But it wasn’t transferred to someone else in the updated will. A supplementary document requests it be buried with him. If you want my opinion, that’s what was stolen.”</p>
<p>Star and Silvia grinned at each other. They said in unison, “Tristan did it.”</p>
<p>Zee laughed. “Exactly.”</p>
<p>Silvia said, “So, then, what do we do about it?”</p>
<p>Well, I do what I do best.” Star was grinning. “I make them talk to each other. We find someplace we can all meet. Bring Tristan, Tatienne, she’s his sister and on his side, Aaron, and Henri. We sit them all down and have a talk.”</p>
<p>“Well, there’s just one problem with that,” Zee said. “The tail that detective has on you.”</p>
<p>“I forgot about that.” Star grimaced. “Well, I’m not about to lead the cops to Tristan. So we need to lose them.”</p>
<p>The three of them talked it over and devised a plan.</p>
<p>Tonight, they'd contact Aaron to get him, Henri, and Tatienne to the meeting spot in Chessman Park. Zee picked it out. There were trees to hide among, a lot of exits, plenty of open space for them to see cops coming, and e knew a safehouse nearby.</p>
<p>Zee would call up eir contacts and see if e could get word out to Tristan about this. Tomorrow morning, they'd leave with Zee and lose their tail and Silvia would go about her day like normal and lose any tails she would get separately. Once their tail was sufficiently lost, they'd go to the park and they'd all talk it out.</p>
<p>They texted Aaron. <i>aaron. chessman park tmmrw. bring tatienne. </i><i>cn rslve evrthng. mke sure henri is wth u.</i></p>
<p>Zee was on eir burner phone with a contact speaking in hushed tones. The call wrapped up. Tristan was at one of the houseless encampments in town. Zee’s contacts could get em to the meeting.</p>
<p>Zee sat down on their bed. “So, then, what do we do all night?”</p>
<p>Star said, “Uh. Chat, I suppose?”</p>
<p>Zee and Silvia both nodded.</p>
<p>Silvia said, “Sounds like a plan.”</p>
<hr>
<p>Star woke to a sizzling sound.</p>
<p>They rubbed their eyes. “Zee?”</p>
<p>“Not just em,” Silvia said. “But e’s the one making breakfast.”</p>
<p>They yawned. “I’m not fully awake, yet. Don’t expect me to remember who all stayed the night.”</p>
<p>The three of them ate Zee’s eggs. They were eggs in a basket this morning.</p>
<p>Silvia left first. They listened as her motorcycle drove off. Zee rummaged through their clothes until e found what e was searching for.</p>
<p>E held up an old jacket with a tiger on the back. “Do you care about this?”</p>
<p>Star shook their head and Zee handed it to them. They put it on and headed out the front door.</p>
<p>They took the bus. Zee took them on a circuitous route. They passed through Union Station three times. Star could barely follow it.</p>
<p>They got out at Denver Metro University. There was a crowd of students walking to classes.</p>
<p>“Hold my hand,” Zee said. “We shouldn’t risk getting separated in the crowd.”</p>
<p>Star took it and the two of them melted into the crowd. They followed some students into the science building. Zee led them through the building to a lab.</p>
<p>Star whispered, “So what are we doing here?”</p>
<p>Zee pointed at a bucket. “Dump the jacket into the chemical waste disposal. People will assume someone got chemicals on it and destroy it. Then we can leave through a different exit and disappear into the crowd.”</p>
<p>They gave em side eye.</p>
<p>“What?” E said. “You said you didn’t care about the jacket.”</p>
<p>They shrugged and disposed of the jacket. They took eir hand, again, and the two of them walked away. They left through a different exit than they entered through. They boarded the bus several blocks away from the university. They sat in the back of the bus.</p>
<p>Star leaned in to Zee. “So that got rid of our tail?”</p>
<p>Zee nodded. “If they followed all that, then they deserve a promotion.”</p>
<p>They breathed out. Tension left their shoulders. “Thank you. I can rely on you for this sort of thing.”</p>
<p>Zee grinned. “That’s what friends are for.”</p>
<p>They reached the park in twenty minutes. Someone threw a frisbee on the other side, barely visible through the trees surrounding the park. No one else was there. They had arrived early.</p>
<hr>
<p>“So what do you think will happen?” Zee said. “Like, when Henri meets his son.”</p>
<p>Star shrugged. “I’m not trying to get him to do any singular particular thing. That’s not the point. Reconciliation, forgiveness, and repentance can only come from the wronged party and the person in the wrong.”</p>
<p>Zee nodded. “Right, I get that. I get you’re not trying to control their behavior. I’m not asking what you want to happen. But what do you predict?”</p>
<p>“Well. Uh...” Star stared at their feet for a moment. “I guess I hadn’t actually thought about that. Probably there will be some confusion and some yelling. But I’ll be here to try to keep things calm, and so will Aaron.”</p>
<p>“So why will it work now?” Zee said. “I mean, both of them have surely yelled at each other before. No doubt there were mediators as well. And that’s without adding graverobbery to the mix.”</p>
<p>“Well... I guess... Uh...” Star bit their lower lip. “I guess I don’t know.”</p>
<p>Zee shrugged. “It’s worth a shot. But you should at least think of that sort of thing before starting.”</p>
<p>Star nodded.</p>
<p>They stood there for awhile. Both leaned on the same tree. The wind passed through, sending a chill through the air for a moment. Star considered what Zee had said.</p>
<p><i>Surely you can't be suggesting that you can talk your way out of every spiritual situation.</i></p>
<p>They hadn't considered the implications to that at the time. Not really. They had told Aaron that he had missed their point, but, really, they had missed his point. They didn't need to stop trying. They didn't need to go into the situation assuming it would devolve into conflict. But they certainly needed to be prepared for that possibility.</p>
<p><i>And what happens when I can’t?</i> The thought hung over them and the situation. They might talk their way through this situation. And the next. And the next. But they’ll eventually find a situation where they can’t do that. When that happens, they needed to be prepared.</p>
<p>Zee nudged them gently. “Hey, Star.”</p>
<p>Silvia was resting against her motorcycle smoking a cigarette. They walked over.</p>
<p>Hey, Silvia,” they said. “Can I have one of those cigarettes?”</p>
<p>Silvia handed one over with a grin. They lit it up and leaned against the motorcycle as well.</p>
<p>Star took a long drag from their cigarette. “Do you think this will work?”</p>
<p>She raised an eyebrow. “What? You mean channeling Henri?”</p>
<p>They shook their head. “No. Getting them to talk. Do you think they’ll, y’know, see each others’ perspective? Listen at all to each other, even.”</p>
<p>Silvia shrugged. “It’s been awhile since I talked with my parents. Don’t know if a priest and a psychic taking me to a park and channeling the dead spirit of them would help things between us. But I’m not sure what choice we have and it’s a bit late for second guessing.”</p>
<p>Star nodded. Another drag from the cigarette. “I should have thought about that before making this plan. Not even that. Before taking on this case. I need to be more prepared for when situations fall apart, right?”</p>
<p>“Maybe you do,” Silvia said. “But, right now, you have more important things to worry about. Aaron is here.”</p>
<p>Star raised their head from their cigarette. Aaron’s car was pulling over. Three people got out of the car. Two men used the same door. They felt the second man more than they saw him. They waved the three of them over.</p>
<p>Tatienne said, “What am I doing here? I talked to you yesterday and the Father wasn’t clear about what I’m supposed to be coming here about.”</p>
<p>They grinned at her. “All will become clear when our final guest gets here.”</p>
<p>Tatienne began to protest, but Aaron pulled her to the side. Star didn’t object. They didn’t particularly want to deal with her. They leaned back against the motorcycle.</p>
<p>Except it wasn’t just the motorcycle there. Zee stood inches from their body.</p>
<p>E whispered, “He’s nearly here. He’ll be a bit down that way among the trees. Doesn’t know what all is going on.”</p>
<p>Star nodded. They raised their voice. “Hey, everyone. Our guest is here. Come with me.”</p>
<p>They turned and walked toward where Zee had indicated. Feet hit pavement behind them.</p>
<p>It wasn’t far before they saw a man moving his head jerkily at nothing in particular who they assumed was Tristan and a familiar figure who was like a goth who just left Hot Topic. It clasped its hands behind its head, accentuating its bleached white hair, and its grin showing its pearly white teeth.</p>
<p>“So, Zee,” Star said. “When you said you knew someone who could get him here, you meant Ezra?”</p>
<p>Zee ginned at them. “You said Tatienne seemed to be interested in Thelema, so I figured calling one of your occultist friends would work. And it did.”</p>
<p>They nodded and walked up to Tristan and Ezra.</p>
<p>“Hi, Tristan,” they said. “It’s very nice to meet you. Please don’t freak out.”</p>
<p>Tristan locked eyes with Ezra then Star then Tatienne behind them all.</p>
<p>He said, “Oh. This is about...”</p>
<p>“The special guest is Tristan?” Tatienne glared at Star. “What are you trying to pull here?”</p>
<p>Star smiled weakly at Tatienne. “You’re not going to like what I do next. Please don’t freak out.”</p>
<p>Voices overlapped with each other. They took a deep breath, counting in and out. The voices made the breathing difficult. But they pushed through it. In and out.</p>
<p>Their voice cut through the noise. “HENRI! HENRI! HENRI!”</p>
<p>They were Henri. They examined Tatienne and Tristan and frowned.</p>
<p>“Is this really a good time for me to be here, Father Aaron?”</p>
<p>Aaron shrugged. “This isn’t my plan, Henri.”</p>
<p>They nodded. “Well, if I’m to be here, I guess I should say hi to my kids.”</p>
<p>A laugh broke out. The person next to their son was laughing and grinning. It was Ezra. They knew that somehow.</p>
<p>“Star always knows how to make things so interesting,” Ezra said. “I’m glad I went along with this. That, Tristan, is your father’s spirit in my friend’s body.”</p>
<p>Tristan blinked at them. Then he glared and stepped forward.</p>
<p>A loud whack and pain consumed their jaw. They fell to the group.</p>
<p>Tristan glared down at them. “Hi, dad.”</p>
<p>Henri glared back up. “After all I did for you, this is how you-”</p>
<p>“All you did for him?” Tatienne yelled. “The fuck are you talking about, dad? Do you mean when you called the cops on your ‘psycho’ son? Or do you mean when you told him you were going to send him to an institution?”</p>
<p>They sat up. “Yes. I mean when I did my best to help my son deal with his madness by allowing the cops to help him with a crisis I was incapable of helping with and attempting to get him psychiatric care.”</p>
<p>Tristan stared off to the side at something they couldn’t see. He said, “I needed love and care. I didn’t need to be locked up. I’m not dangerous. The biggest dangers to me is how others treat me. Others like you.”</p>
<p>They stood up. “You were seeing things, talking to people. You were... You are sick.”</p>
<p>Father Aaron put a hand on their shoulder. “Henri. Is that really how you want to treat your son after so long of not seeing him?”</p>
<p>They glared back at him. “I should just take it when he punches me?”</p>
<p>“Yes, you should,” he said. “Remember Luke 6:29. ‘If someone slaps you on one cheek, turn to them the other also. If someone takes your coat, do not withhold your shirt from them.’ More so given he is your son.”</p>
<p>They frowned. “The Bible says a lot of nice things. But, if I’m to raise a son, I need to be able to do for him what he needs.”</p>
<p>“Son, I think what he needs,” Aaron said, “is for you to listen to him. We are all born fallible and it doesn’t do well to assume you know what’s best. Only God above does.”</p>
<p>They nodded. “I don’t know what’s best, Father. You’re right about that. But the doctors did and the doctors told me that he would improve in the facility, with the medication he would get there. I listened to them.”</p>
<p>They turned to face Tristan and stepped toward him. “And you, son, thought you knew better than the doctors. Your utter arrogance, enabled by your sister. You need to learn to listen to your father when he is doing what’s right for you.”</p>
<p>Tatienne glared at them. “Fuck off with that bullshit. You were doing what was convenient for your image, not what was best for Tristan.”</p>
<p>Henri said, “You always were very kind, Tatienne. But you never knew how to do what was needed.”</p>
<p>Tatienne’s face contorted. They didn’t hear what was said next. Their head was cloudy. Star opened their mouth. Henri closed it.</p>
<p>“Stay out of this, Star,” they said. “You wanted me to talk to my children, then you let me.”</p>
<p>Ezra cut through the yelling. “Old man. If Star wants their body back, you should let them have it.”</p>
<p>Its eyes locked with theirs. Pain shot through their body. They were Star.</p>
<p>“Henri,” Star said, “I didn’t bring you here so you could yell at your children. I brought you here so you could <i>listen</i> to them. Shut up and listen.”</p>
<p>They were Henri, again.</p>
<p>“Well, Star,” Henri said. “I appreciate your condescension, but these are my children. I will raise them as I wish and you will stop interfering.”</p>
<p>They felt the clouds in their head again. They turned their head away from Ezra and stepped toward his children.</p>
<p>“I am your father,” they said. “Everyone interfering has forgotten that. You are my responsibility, not theirs. I will take care of you and make what choices are necessary to raise you well.”</p>
<p>Tatienne glared at them. “Get back to me when you start making those choices, then. The only choices you’ve made have been to <i>control</i> us, not to raise us well.”</p>
<p>They stared down at Tristan. He was curled up on the ground with hands on his ears.</p>
<p>Henri pointed to him. “This is exactly what I was trying to fix by sending him to that hospital. He would’ve gotten the care he needed.”</p>
<p>Tatienne stepped forward. “Maybe if you didn’t yell at him his psychosis wouldn’t be-”</p>
<p>“Everyone shut up,” Zee said. Eir voice wasn’t particularly loud, but it pierced through the other voices. “All of your yelling has gotten the attention of the cops. And, if you don’t mind, we have a thief, his sister, and someone who was skulking around the scene of the crime, here.”</p>
<p>Everyone turned to stare.</p>
<p>“Now, I know I wasn’t followed,” Zee continued. “But I’m not so certain that the Father here wasn’t. The detective doubtless can put together what’s happening. We need to wrap this up and leave.”</p>
<p>Henri turned back and stared at Tristan. “<i>You</i> robbed my grave?”</p>
<p>Tristan raised his head. His face was stained with tears. “I-it was p-promised to me.”</p>
<p>“And, then,” they said, “you ran away. Did you expect that you wouldn’t be cut out of the will?”</p>
<p>Tristan grimaced. “It was promised to me. It was promised to me. It was promised to me.”</p>
<p>He started to cry again.</p>
<p>“You were <i>buried</i> with that?” Tatienne said. “What gave you the right to take that locket with you to your grave?”</p>
<p>“It was mine,” they said. “Surely I can make the decisions about it I deemed fit.”</p>
<p>Tatienne took a long, deep breath. “Maybe that’s the case, but does that make it right?”</p>
<p>They raised their chin. “It was mine, not his, never his.”</p>
<p>“Maybe, maybe not,” Silvia said. “But that doesn’t particularly matter, now. Fact is, he has it and either he goes to prison or you figure something out with him. We don’t have much time to spare.”</p>
<p>They stepped back from Tristan. “It’s true. I don’t think you should see the inside of a jail cell over this. It’s not for the cops to deal with. It’s a family matter.”</p>
<p>Henri took a deep breath in. They were Star.</p>
<p>They crouched down. “Hey, Tristan. I’m on your side with this. Your father really should’ve left this with you.”</p>
<p>Tristan slowly nodded. They reached out their hand and held it above his shoulder, not touching. He nodded again. They gently put their hand on his shoulder.</p>
<p>“I think you should get the locket,” they said. “It’s clearly important to you. But, right now, you need to avoid going to jail. The cops will be trying to find anyone who’s connected with your father to pin the blame on. If not you, then your sister might get the blame. Do you understand that?”</p>
<p>Tristan nodded to them.</p>
<p>Star smiled. “Aaron here can talk to your mother for you. Once this is wrapped up, the locket will go to her and she should be able to decide what’s done with it. The two of us can make sure you get it, like you want, and keep everything within the family, like your father wants. Does this sound ok to you?”</p>
<p>Tristan sat there doing nothing for a bit. Then he nodded.</p>
<p>They held out their free hand. “May I have the locket?”</p>
<p>Tristan rummage through their pocket and placed a plain silver locket in their hand. On the back was etched Tristan’s name and inside it was a picture of Tristan, much younger than he is now, on one side and an older woman who resembled Tatienne on the other side.</p>
<p>They gently closed their hand around it. “Thank you, Tristan. Me and Aaron can make sure this gets resolved.”</p>
<p>They felt something against their back. They were Henri.</p>
<p>“Thank you, Star,” Henri said. “But I can take it from here.”</p>
<p>They stood up and walked over to Aaron and handed over the locket.</p>
<p>“Tristan, Tatienne,” they said, “it will do us no good for the police to find us here.”</p>
<p>They reached down their hand to help Tristan up. He did nothing.</p>
<p>“Son. I know I hurt you.” They hesitated. “I can’t change that. But, right now, I need you to come with me so that Star’s effort isn’t in vain.”</p>
<p>He still did nothing.</p>
<p>They stared down at him, then sighed deeply. “I’m sorry, son. I shouldn’t have taken that with me to my grave. Now can you please come with me?”</p>
<p>Tristan hesitated. He took their hand and rose. They led Tristan away from the scene.</p>
<p>Ezra placed a hand on their shoulder. “Hey, old man. I know a place they can hide.”</p>
<p>They stared at it. “I would like to help my children get there.”</p>
<p>“Yeah, sure. Whatever,” Ezra said. “Just come with me.”</p>
<p>Ezra led the three of them away from the scene and down a side street. As they walked it explained that a friend knew some people who lived in the area which would work as a safe house while others dealt with the cops.</p>
<p>They didn’t take long before arriving at the house. Unlike the houses around it, this one was drab. The lawn wasn’t as neatly mowed. The facade wasn’t as well maintained. Ezra knocked on the door.</p>
<p>A young person answered. Henri wasn’t sure what to make of them. They were dressed eccentrically and wore strange make up.</p>
<p>“Hey, Erin,” Ezra said. “I’m a friend of Zee’s. E told you about me on the phone.”</p>
<p>Erin nodded. “E said we might need to give some people a place to stay for a bit. Cop involvement. But we’re always happy to do a favor for Zee.”</p>
<p>It nodded. “Yeah. Well, got some people here for you.”</p>
<p>They helped Tristan and Tatienne into the house.</p>
<p>“Henri,” Ezra said. “You should stay here with your kids. I need Star.”</p>
<p>Henri nodded. They were Star. The air moved around them into the house.</p>
<p>Ezra grabbed Star’s arm and dragged them further down the road.</p>
<p>“Hey, wait,” Star said. “Where are we going?”</p>
<p>Ezra glared at them. “To the meeting place Zee set up for us all. We’re going to wait for Aaron there and let our friends back there help those two. But, more importantly, we need to talk.”</p>
<p>They followed along and stared at the ground.</p>
<p>“Listen, Star,” it said. “You were useless against Henri back there controlling you. I intervened, once, but I can’t always be there and Henri figured out pretty quick how to avoid my <i>malocchio</i>, so you didn’t get control back until he let you. You need to fix that.”</p>
<p>Star nodded. “Sometimes I can’t just talk my way out of situations like that. I need to be prepared for the worst.”</p>
<p>“Exactly,” Ezra said. “You don’t like to throw your force around, but sometimes you need to be able to do so. And I can help with that. We’re friends.”</p>
<p>Star agreed and they made their way through the streets. They walked for more than an hour. Ezra didn’t check over its shoulder. They expected it didn’t need to. But they did. No one followed them.</p>
<p>Zee and Silvia were waiting up for them at a bench next to Silvia’s motorcycle. They greeted them with a hug from each. Aaron showed up not long after in his car.</p>
<p>“I talked to the cops,” Aaron said. “I told them I had been working to get the locket back for the family and cited ecclesiastical privilege. They were pissed, but I was able to call my lawyer and he got them to back off. I can talk to the family and make sure no charges get pressed. This will be a mess, but more trouble than its worth for the cops to keep pursuing.”</p>
<p>Star nodded and thanked him. They breathed a sigh of relief. They sat on the bench and leaned against Silvia. Zee sat next to them and leaned on them. Exhaustion washed over them. They closed their eyes and just let themself rest.</p>
<hr>
<p class="align-center">If you enjoy these stories, please consider pledging monthly money to my <a href="https://www.patreon.com/deathpigeon">Patreon</a> or one time donations with <a href="https://venmo.com/Zara-Storm">Venmo</a> or <a href="https://cash.app/$deathpigeon">Cashapp</a>. Thank you.</p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/ghost-crimes/">Read more Ghost Crimes.</a></p>
<p class="align-center">Previous: <a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/double-murder-ghost-crimes-1/">DOUBLE MURDER.</a></p>
<p class="align-center">Next: <a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/the-fire-with-no-name-ghost-crimes-3/">THE FIRE WITH NO NAME</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Farewell (Ghost Crimes)</title>
        <author>
            <name>Zara RW Storm</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/farewell-ghost-crimes/"/>
        <id>https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/farewell-ghost-crimes/</id>
            <category term="Ghost Crimes"/>

        <updated>2021-09-06T21:22:17-06:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Content Warning: Pet Loss, Spirit Possession Star knelt at the freshly dug earth. Death filled the space, but not as a physical feeling. There wasn’t some cold or smell or vibration that told them that someone dead was here. Instead, there was a gnawing sense&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p class="align-center">Content Warning: Pet Loss, Spirit Possession</p>
<hr>
<p>Star knelt at the freshly dug earth. Death filled the space, but not as a physical feeling. There wasn’t some cold or smell or vibration that told them that someone dead was here. Instead, there was a gnawing sense of the inevitability of the end clawing at the back of their head.</p>
<p>They look up at their client, Lyuba. “I’m so sorry for your loss.”</p>
<p>She took a long drag from her cigarette. The lines on her face deepened. “Thank you. My poor baby Inna...” She covered her face as it convulsed slightly.</p>
<p>Star let the silence hang in the air. They knew her pain.</p>
<p>Her hand left her face and she was back to not showing them anything. “I miss her so much...”</p>
<p>Star nodded. “Before we start, I do need to know what you intend to do during the channeling. You will be speaking to Inna, but she’ll be in my body.”</p>
<p>Lyuba nodded slowly. “I just need to tell her I love her. Give her little scritches. Know that she still loves me.”</p>
<p>Star closed their eyes and concentrated on their breathing. Energy flowed along their skin like mud being pulled across the ground. It accumulated around their middle finger as a pressure on the outer joint, a slight tug on it from the small grave. They got up. The tug didn’t impede their movement, but it told them where the grave was. “We should probably go inside for this.”</p>
<p>Lyuba rented the back room of the house. The floor was strewn with clothes. Clothes that stunk. She didn’t have much in terms of furniture, only a bed and a dresser. But she had a cat tower and a lot of cat toys. She had clearly spent more money buying things for Inna than herself.</p>
<p>Star cleared a spot of dirty clothes and sat down crosslegged. “In just a moment I’m going to be channeling Inna into my body. This will still be my body and I can take control back at any time. But the spirit of your dead cat will be inside of me. She will remember everything from when she was alive and she’ll act like she did in life. Are you ready for that?”</p>
<p>Lyuba nodded. Star closed their eyes and began to control their breathing.</p>
<p>"Inna..." Star said. "Inna... Inna... Inna!"</p>
<p>The pressure around their middle finger thrummed. They pulled against it and the pressure let up, as if something had come loose.</p>
<p>They were Inna.</p>
<p>Their eyes opened and they looked around. They leaned forward and clawed at the ground, but their claws didn’t catch on it like they used to.</p>
<p>“Inna?”</p>
<p>The voice was soft. They were used to it booming. They looked up. She looked down at them with her soft grey eyes, crinkled from her smile. Their love overwhelmed them and they crawled up to her.</p>
<p>The soft voice spoke again. “Lyublyu tebe.”</p>
<p>Her arms wrapped around them. They felt their love returned.</p>
<p>They murred and rubbed their face against their mom. She gave them scritches on their head.</p>
<p>“I’m so sorry. If there was anything I could have done to help you...”</p>
<p>They didn’t know how they understood her, but they did. There was nothing that could’ve been done. In the end, they hadn’t wanted to keep going. Life had become too much and they didn’t want to continue.</p>
<p>Their face was wet and they didn’t understand why. They stayed there for awhile, their mother’s arms around them and water flowing down their cheeks.</p>
<p>Finally, their mother let go of them. Her voice came out strange. It was weak and cracked. “I would like to end this session.”</p>
<p>They were Star again.</p>
<p>Silence hung for several moments before they spoke. “She really loved you. I could feel what she felt, and there was an overwhelming feeling of love. You were her mother.”</p>
<p>Tears ran down Lyuba’s face. Her voice came out cracked when she finally spoke. “Did she blame me? For her death?”</p>
<p>Star shook their head. “It was her time to go. She’d lived a good life, but she couldn’t handle living too much longer.”</p>
<p>Lyuba nodded slowly. “Thank you.”</p>
<hr>
<p class="align-center"><a href="https://deathpigeon.github.io/zara-rw-storm/ghost-crimes/">Read more Ghost Crimes.</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
